Fairy Sister
Wanwan
Really good work
No more
sorry
I'm late
You don't
Lucky Sister
Have you ever seen me?
Ha ha ha ha
沈婉这小公爷身受重伤还替你送死
True love
It's really touching.
turn out to be
You just used me to frame Xie Yujie
You know that there is no personal relationship between us.
Why do you enter my innocence?
The 7th is our wedding day
Someone has been brought to kill me
Chen Wan
You have occupied the daughter of Lian'er Shenfu for so many years.
If it weren't for Xie Yujie's love for you
I can use you to take back the Xie family's military power.
Eliminate the thorn in the side of the Xie family
How could I lie to you and say I want to marry you?
the
It's what you deserve
Prince, I'm scared.
Don't be afraid, Lian'er, I'm here
father
What are you yelling about?
If it weren't for the fact that you are the doctor's apprentice
Can heal Lian'er's face
I would have killed you long ago.
I wasted my troops to kill your biological parents and silence them.
你们骗我治好沈莲的伤
Tell him to go back
He was having an affair with my fiancé
Shen Zhengyi
Why did you kill my biological parents?
You beasts will die.
Xie Yuejie
You are not alone on the road to the underworld
Lian Er
I dare not
His hand was injured and he couldn't pull it.
I will teach you
God has eyes
I actually went back to six years ago
When I was studying at the Holy Mountain
It was not easy to find my biological parents
In this life, I want to get there before the Shen family persecutes me.
Save Mom and Dad
Dad and Mom are in danger here now
I'll take you to a safe place.
I have been planning for revenge for a long time
Clouds surging everywhere
Finally found the gods ahead of time
This is beautiful
Really good
Oh, so ugly.
Go quickly
Walk
This first step
Send the unhealed spirits back to the God's Palace
Ugly face
A daughter who behaves rudely
The God's Mansion was turned upside down
I can take this opportunity to disintegrate the Divine Palace.
Protect your family and friends
Revenge of past life
My God King is back
The old lady is here today to become the disciple of Mu Xianshan
The day when the holy garments returned from study
Congratulations, madam.
The Shen family is going to have another queen
Hahaha good
grandmother
Mother
沈宛有罪
沈宛不是沈家女
Year after year
What are you doing? Get up!
沈宛不配
Sui Sui, someone is bullying you, Sui Sui
You tell my second brother
Who bullies you?
Brother, kill them.
Sui Sui, what nonsense are you talking about?
Don't scare me.
You are my only precious daughter.
Mom, I'm on my way home.
Save a woman
This girl's name is Lianzi
Born on the same day as me
She looks very similar to her mother
Similar appearance
There are many people born on the same day of the same month of the same year.
Cuicui, you hurt yourself
It also worries my grandmother and mother.
You get up first.
Did your mother fall into trouble in Anlin Village when she was pregnant?
Staying at a farmer's home
This woman is from Anlin Village
He has the same longevity lock as me.
This is where the distinction begins.
I became suspicious
To find the truth
He went to Anlin Village in person.
Originally the mother
Wrong baby
ah
The truth is that your husband despises you for giving birth to a monster.
The lovely child born by the farmer was thrown away.
The Shen family lied until they died in their last life.
I am the child of Shen family.
The bloodline of the Shen family must not be lost outside
Calculate
Sui Sui, please go back to your room and rest first.
We will make our own decision on this matter
I've loved her for so many years.
It turns out that he is not Shen's biological child.
Mother, let's go find my sister.
We really can't let the Shen family's legitimate wife wander around
right
Go and inform old lady Zhengyi
You don't want to take Miss back
沈婉貌美端庄
She is the best choice for the future queen.
We have to stabilize her first.
If that child is not as good as her
No need
The Xie family stood in front of the Prince's team many times
The prince is already afraid of
There are ghosts around
Please be careful, I am not a bad person
We will meet if we are destined to meet
Xie Yujin
沈莲未入府
There may be variables
I can't meet you offline yet
Hope for peace
沈尚书回家看到丑陋的亲生女儿
How angry would that be?
The nonsense grandson is the disciple of Yu Sheng
Read the books of sages
Proficient in music, chess, calligraphy and painting
Having such a smart and clever daughter
Why did you bring that child back?
Master, this is what I said
I don't want to take back my own flesh and blood.
Or Master?
你一早就知道沈万的真实身份
My knowledge and medical skills can help my Shen family rise to prominence.
Father Mother
I've already taken it back
You see, you can
But don't make it public
Otherwise, my Shen family will perish.
What are you doing?
Where are you taking me? Let me go
oops
Kneel down before you speak
Really not as knowledgeable as Shenwan
You raise your head
Meeting parents
She even covered her face without any manners.
It's really unacceptable
Ahhh
I didn't do anything wrong
Don't hit me
Feng Er took him away
Give it to Aunt Song, it's my father
ah
Ah, sir, you said I
How could she give birth to an ugly monster?
I also want to ask you
What evil have you done?
You know that my Shen family is going to continue to serve the throne.
He looks like that
I sent him to the palace.
All of us in the Shen family will be beheaded
So I found a farmer to replace him
master
A poor peasant child
Why waste my hard work for more than ten years?
必须要把沈万赶出去
沈万他必须是我沈家的嫡长母
The future queen
若想留下沈林
He and Sui Sui must be called twin girls.
Join us in the Extreme Ceremony
otherwise
沈莲绝不可能活着进沈家
Second Brother
It just so happened that I won a horse with my horse riding and archery
I want to give it to my second brother
I wish my second brother a successful imperial examination
Hahahaha
Thank you for your reassurance
Although his mother ordered him to stay
And I want to take him to the Gigi ceremony
But you will never
It is Jijili, the daughter of the God's Mansion
Mo Junlin will also come that day
让他提前见到沈莲
The Shen family is one step closer to destruction
Where is the horse? Take brother to see it.
In Majiu
You ride your horse along the long street
My second brother's legs were broken
I want you to have a taste of him too.
The Shen family drama has just begun
Look, I won't beat you to death.
Stop, why are you hitting me?
I'm so mad
Help! Kill people!
2 Miss Madam confessed
There can be no mistakes in tomorrow's fund
You have to learn etiquette first
What to explain
Didn't you just find Shen Qing?
Tell me about my life
But none of you take me seriously
Shouting
What a disgrace
Mother Song asked you to teach etiquette
That's how you teach.
The second brother and sister never learned the rules
No need to be so harsh on Nanny Song
There will be many distinguished guests in tomorrow's collection
Many people and many opinions
My sister's face
It's better to put on some makeup
Sui Sui Second Brother
I'm so lucky to have you as my sister.
The Shen family has hope.
There is me
The Shen family will forget
Aunt Song
There are so many people
Ha ha
Yes, Miss Two
Now I put on makeup
No marks can be seen
Please pay attention
After attending the assembly ceremony
I went back to the house to prevent the hot weather from causing my makeup to fall off.
I see
Haha, this lady
Capable of both literature and martial arts
She is indeed a model of a noble lady in Beijing.
自从沈妹妹去圣山学医后
We never met again.
沈妹妹幼时就娇嫩可爱
Now she should be a goddess who can topple a country.
Where did this hag come from?
A woman of standard size actually competed in public
No rules
It's so unteachable.
Picturesque
Out of this world
This is the fiancée my mother chose for me.
你是沈妹妹吧
果然像沈夫人一样秀丽可人
Unlike them, who are dissolute and have no manners
yes
His Royal Highness
Pay your respects to His Highness
I have met His Royal Highness the Crown Prince.
Today is your Jijili
This is the palace that my mother specially built for you.
A token of my gift to you
Your Highness
This is mistaking the second young lady for the eldest young lady.
His Royal Highness
So swaggering
No courtesy
还是沈妹妹清秀之礼
Suitable for being a princess
Today is a few days later
The Queen Mother will summon your father to the palace to discuss the marriage.
I want to fly up to the tree and become a phoenix
I will complete you
Only you are close to Mo Junli
The Shen family and the prince cooperate to avoid chaos
After the relationship breaks down
It is convenient to defeat them one by one
His Royal Highness
This hairpin is so exquisite
It must be very expensive.
不是说沈宛是准太子妃
Future Empress
Why does the prince have this attitude?
难道沈宛被厌弃了
The prince is the Shen family's support
If the prince is gone
The Shen family is about to be finished
Your Highness, please forgive me.
This attitude should have been
You ladies,
No courtesy
Playing around in other people's houses
What a disgrace
He also ignored the protagonist Kamimaru in the attack
His Royal Highness
The servants are just playing with Miss Shen.
臣女沈宛见过太子表哥
What
You are the queen mother
被定为太子妃的沈宛
So who is he?
她是我的双生妹妹沈莲
Chen Nu's parents
Today we will announce this news to you all
从未听说沈小姐还有个妹妹
Sister Lian has been weak since childhood
Always pampered on the farm
Now that I am feeling better, I have come to Beijing.
You are not allowed to bully her.
Come
Even my sister is so stunning
Elegant
On the contrary, it's you
Not following the rules
No courtesy
I think you are the one who bullied her.
Your Highness, please forgive me.
I know I am wrong
snort
Change your ostentatious and uncivilized behavior
Meet His Royal Highness
Dad, help me
Daughter's Matter
I bumped into the prince's cousin
Your Highness, the eldest daughter of an official
Studied medicine with the Medical Saint for 6 years
Read the Four Books and Five Classics
Good at reciting poems
I'm afraid I haven't seen His Highness for a long time today.
I feel frustrated because I miss you
Please don't blame your highness.
Get up, everyone.
Lord Shen, you should discipline him more.
Multiple births
Even my sister is so gentle
Your Highness is really poor and weak
I have never stopped taking medicine for the past ten years.
That's why it's so quiet
Let His Highness mistakenly think that I am not in good health
Don't like me anymore
What should I do, Dad?
I'm not sick. I'm in good health.
Why did you lie to His Royal Highness?
Mr. Shen, how dare you lie to me?
The prince's cousin sister Lian has indeed been weak since childhood
Shenfu takes good care of
The body is getting better
A father loves his daughter dearly
Prince cousin, please don't misunderstand
Lian Meimei needs Jiang Yang
If anything happened to him
I will definitely hold the ministers accountable
Your Highness, rest assured
I will definitely do it.
The prince ignored this ugly guy and fell in love with him
Your Highness Gigi
The ceremony is about to begin
Your Highness, please take a step forward.
Ling Er please
Isn't that Young Master Xie from the Duke of Zhenguo's Mansion?
Today is so lively.
This young master Xie is indeed a young master from an aristocratic family.
So fit
Still so graceful
He is not inferior to the prince.
Xie Yujin at this moment
It was his best years before he got seriously ill.
Only by letting him avoid the risks of Huaizhong Mansion
Only then can he change the fate of him and the Xie family.
I wonder if he received my letter?
elder sister
I have something to tell you
Let's go to the lake
good
I like His Royal Highness
I want to be a princess
Please give it to me.
I know
Everyone in the Shen family wants to send you to the palace to be the Crown Princess.
Your father praised you so much.
But it devalues ​​me to nothing
Please let me
Why should I let you
Can't you see?
The prince likes me
He hates you
Who do you like to hate?
Who he likes
The Shen family and the Eastern Palace only recognize me as the Crown Princess offline.
If you like him so much
When I entered the East Palace
How about letting him take you as his concubine?
Why should I be a concubine?
I want to be a princess.
This is the Prince's Palace
Do you have the hairpin I gave you?
Who cares?
Queen
My aunt would send someone to my house every year.
I don't know how much I have saved from traveling so hard
How come you forgot who rescued you?
Poor health
The brain is not good either.
You stop
ah
Oh no! The eldest and second daughter fell into the water.
What
Madam, something is wrong.
The second lady pushed the eldest lady into the water
His Royal Highness the Crown Prince and Young Master Xie both jumped into the water to save people.
The lady and the second son were startled and fell off the horse
The horse's legs were broken.
The doctor said that if he didn't amputate
My legs will die.
The indulgent doctor is
wrong
Sui Sui is a disciple of the miracle doctor
He will surely save
Shameless
Sorry for the inconvenience.
殿下还是先关心沈二小姐吧
My humble servant
看沈二小姐冷的都快钻进您衣服里了
you
Lin Meimei
Let's go
Many thanks
Miss Shen
Thank you, mother.
It was Xie who offended me just now.
I will definitely shut everyone's mouth
Don't let others ruin your innocence
Xie said goodbye first
Thank you, Lord, can you help me save someone?
The Horse Father of the God's Mansion
Where's the groom?
How could the Second Young Master be injured so seriously?
Bring him to me.
Father
My second brother's injury is serious.
Then I ordered someone to hold
The legs of Mr. Shen's second son are so broken by horse hooves.
Due to excessive blood loss
People are also in a coma
If you want to save your life
Must hijack
The Shen family poured all their efforts into Feng Er.
He must enter the room as an official
Otherwise, the Shen family will have no future.
No, absolutely no amputation.
Mr. Shen, please think twice
Saving the Second Young Master's life is the most important thing
master
Feng'er must live.
Where is Sui Sui Sui Sui?
He is the disciple of the miraculous doctor Ding Chuan
He must have a way to hurry up
Find Sui Sui quickly!
Right, right, right
The eldest daughter was pushed into the lake by the second daughter
After being rescued by Master Xie, he went back to his room to rest.
It's your evil obstacle.
I want to kick him out of the house.
After the second lady was embroidered by His Royal Highness the Crown Prince
My father and second brother are seriously injured.
I'll go bring the fourth sister over here.
Go
Big Brother
I didn't know in my previous life
You have been hiding your identity and protecting me.
Thank you, Governor
Thank you for helping me rescue him.
I'd like to ask you for one more favor.
Please help me get him out of the palace.
Place well
Shenwan must be dangerous
你为何要我救这个伤了沈二的车夫
he
It's your sweetheart
no
I'll explain it to you later
This is a panacea
Eliminate hundreds of poisons and cure thousands of gold
I will definitely repay you in the future
If he doesn't leave the Shen family now
It'll kill him.
Cuicui, open the door quickly!
Your second brother's legs were seriously injured.
I need your healing
quick
Cuicui
Open the door quickly. Open the door quickly.
I can't openly go against the Shen family.
只能通过装病毒来废掉沈长风
ah
Sui Sui, your second brother's legs are seriously injured
Come with me
沈婉
What is your purpose?
Brother, please be gentle
My arm is injured
Injured
Can you still kill two birds with one stone?
The Shen family is really selfish
After being pushed into the water
My arms are powerless
I'm afraid it can't be cured.
what to do
oh
You are a disciple of the divine doctor
Anyone else want it?
I won't give it to you even if I have it.
But I can take this opportunity
加深沈莲和沈家的门盾
Didn't I save Sister Lian on the way back home?
She's used up all the medicine.
Go and have a look
I called her over.
Sui Sui Kuai
Hurry and treat your second brother
Dad can't cure
Aren't you a disciple of the divine doctor?
Why do you say you can't cure it?
Mother was pushed into the pond every year
Injured right hand
Can't move now
What a coincidence, could it be that he is holding a grudge?
Want to take revenge on the Chen family
That's why I don't give you the will of your second brother.
Dad, what are you talking about?
Doctor Luo is here
You can let him treat me.
See if my daughter is sincere
Dr. Luo,
Miss Shen is indeed
Right hand
Need to be cultivated
No distortion
The daughter needs to distort her true self to stop her brother's bleeding
Daughter is useless
Master, what can I do?
Do I really have to untie Feng Er's legs?
ah
Mr. Shen, please make the decision.
I can cure
Li Er, you just said you can abandon your brother
I can choose not to cut off my second brother's legs.
Cure him
Why
Where did this yellow-haired girl come from?
I dare not even show my face
Still dare to speak so arrogantly
You mediocre person
Mingming used black jade paste
Combined with the pills and treatment, you can grow
You don't even know this
Still alive for so many years
Return to the Imperial Doctor
So stupid and cute
Death in the fire pit
joke
You have been an academician of the Imperial Hospital for so many years.
It's in vain
Black Jade Ointment is a magical medicine
You think anyone can have it?
Why
I am you
What's wrong? Are you jealous?
Lian Er
Mother's good daughter
Give your brother medical treatment quickly
Want me to save my second brother
Yes, but you have to agree to one condition.
I want you to drive Shenwang out of the Divine Palace
What
Sister Lian
What did I do wrong?
You're going to kick me out of the house.
You've dominated my life for so many years.
How dare you stay in the Divine Palace?
As long as you're gone
I am the Crown Princess
I can't leave you in the God's Mansion, Father.
The black jade intermittent cream is here
You decide for yourself.
master
Wind
The wind cannot live without legs
no
Can't leave the temple every year
The family will not let me go easily.
Dad, my second brother is in danger now.
If my daughter leaves home, she can save my second brother's life.
My daughter is willing
I promise you
Bring the medicine. If it works, it won't be too late to send him out.
good
So much blood.
It actually stopped the bleeding.
This is amazing
Of course, this is a magic medicine
Father, you should keep your promise.
Xian'er sent your sister out of the house
I'm finally going to fly up to the tree and become a phoenix
I was worried that I couldn't find a chance to leave the house and imprison the demon.
沈莲还算有点用
Year after year
You go back to the Holy Mountain first
Dad and I will definitely take you back.
那个沈烈
The Shen family can no longer stay
You will ask me to come back home.
After all, black jade is intermittently high
不仅救不了沈成松
It will kill me
Thank you, bro
There is money in this bag.
All for you
If you don't ask for money, what do you ask for?
I am a holy yam person
The whole body is poisonous
Don't mess around.
I didn't expect Miss Shen to be afraid sometimes.
There is no malicious intent
Don't be afraid, Miss Shen
Sorry, don't cry.
Thank you, Lord Governor, what can I do for you?
Oh, I have placed the groom outside the city
I have something to ask you
So I came back
Can't you see this?
Kicked out by the Shen family
Why just because you hurt your arm
There is no savior.
As expected, it is the Imperial City Division
Since Lord Xie knows Yuan Yong
Why come to me then?
I want you to help me save someone.
Jiang Lin, the son of a traitor
You were sent by the prince.
how
Lord Xie, do you think I know you are colluding with the rebels?
To kill me
You are not a traitor
I'm afraid that everyone has his own boss
Since Miss Shen is injured and it is inconvenient to treat her
Xie resigned
Secret letter from a few days ago
The Lord has received it.
Xie didn't understand what Miss Shen meant.
The prince has long coveted the Xie family's military power
You rejected my several hints.
Now you are the prince's enemy
Miss Shen is a lady from a noble family.
Know so much
I also know that you died for me
The Xie family died because of me
I also know that the Jiang family is full of loyal and brave people.
Loyalty and perseverance in defending southern Xinjiang
But was slandered by the treacherous Ning
Jiang's achievements are greater than his master's
The Jiang family is full of powerful and scheming officials
The soldiers didn't even know why they died.
This is a secret letter
You are really the prince's man.
I can be yours if necessary.
I can help him
Then I can help you
As long as you believe me
What you want
I don't want anything
I owe you this.
Take this back and give it to him.
Three days later
Bring Jiangling to Puhua Temple
I'll be waiting for you there
Then heal it
After I cure it
It's not too late for you to reply me
See if you want to cooperate with me
Do you believe me?
I'm sorry, Miss.
I will be guilty of this.
Big Brother
Thank you for saving my life, Miss.
Yasui will be ruthless to the eldest lady
Gu Jingan, the eldest son of the Gu family in Anling Village
6 years away from home
Still not back
Big Brother
Dad and mom miss you very much
It's the people from the Shenfu who are chasing us.
Go away, I'll be behind you.
Don't be afraid, brother
It's the Imperial Guards that hunt down rebels.
The Divine Palace is now too busy to take care of itself
I won't send anyone after you.
How do you know my identity?
六年前我便知道自己非沈府亲属
I tried my best to find my parents.
Save my parents from the Shen family thieves
They have now been settled in Huaizhou Prefecture
Can I call you Yan Ning?
Moon Girl
Since I joined the army
I got the news about you at the border.
我求乔庄潜入了沈府
I want to protect you
Now you and I are brothers and sisters
Yin Niang, please come back with me
Big Brother
I can't leave yet
The Shen family is the queen's mother's family
Powerful
Evil-hearted
Leave hastily
I'm afraid the Gu family can't compete with it.
Then I'll stay
I protect you
You go to Huaizhou Prefecture
Take care of your parents' safety
It's only a matter of time before Shen Zhengyi finds them
so
I have someone in Huaizhou Prefecture who can help me
But what can you do?
I want revenge for my second brother.
沈长峰的双腿是因沈莲而断
Shen's family escapes chaos
莫君礼心悦沈莲
No one cares about me offline
It's a good time to avenge my second brother.
Don't worry, Daddy
I will do as you say.
You just need to remember
Whatever happens
My parents and I will be behind you.
good
Is this where Miss Shen should live?
要不是把沈婉赶走了都
I don't know how biased the Shen family will be.
Wow
Start now
These things are mine
Open the door quickly, my second brother is feeling hot all over
Bring something
Follow me
You want to run away with your stuff.
I don't
Better not
I know your medicine was given to you by Sui Sui
Did you know
He was kicked out of the house because of you
Bring your elixir
If I can't cure my second brother's injury
I want your life
Brother, I am your biological sister.
Sister
My second brother is a talent cultivated by the whole family
No one is more important than him.
Say it again
Take your elixir and follow me
Successfully sent away
Brother, check the time
The effect of the black jade ointment has expired
The Shen family should be in chaos now.
It's time for me to go back to the Shen Mansion and add fuel to the fire.
How come Jiang Lin is getting better?
So impatient to find me
You figured I'd come find you
I figured you'd come find me
I didn't expect you to come here to find me
Miss Shen is resourceful
Have you ever considered staying overnight?
Where
Do you need Xie's help?
I was planning to go back to Shen's house.
The young master has arrived
How about you accompany me?
I was fine when I took the medicine in the afternoon.
Why does it get serious at night?
Sir, should we ask Dr. Luo to come over?
闭嘴我已经让肖儿去把沈莲带过来
Someone was also sent to invite Dr. Luo.
You're walking around here.
Are you annoying?
Wind
Look at the wind
What's going on?
You dare to run
I'm going to interrupt you now
Lian'er, you are really a good daughter to your mother.
Fortunately, you are here
Yes, Lian'er is our Shen family's great benefactor.
father
Big brother just bullied me
My hands hurt.
Xiao Er apologizes to your sister
What on earth is going on?
Mr. Shen's second son
This is a wound infection
Both legs must be amputated as soon as possible
Otherwise, you will die.
Isn't the medicine getting better?
What is going on?
Did you ever take any medicine?
He gave Feng Er medicine
Feng Er vomited blood
What medicine did you take?
I have no idea
This magic pill must have been given to me by him
He poisoned the medicine.
He wants to frame me
Kamimaru
Find him now.
Too late
Lord Shen must have his legs amputated immediately.
You quack doctor
Then you should amputate his limb immediately.
Shut up, you have no right to speak here.
Lord Shen, please make a decision quickly.
If I were to amputate the Second Young Master on my own initiative
I am afraid of dying in the mouth of your daughter.
Must hijack
In case of death
It will definitely be counted on me.
I am also from the Shen family.
I order you to amputate his leg.
Stop messing around
If it weren't for your second brother
How could it hurt so badly?
Let's see who dares to touch him today.
Prince brother
My son is dying.
You should have him amputated.
Save his life
I order you to amputate immediately.
If something happens
The Palace's Battle
Thank you so much Lord
The Agreement of Puhua Temple
Live up to the high expectations of the Lord
You still have to go back
The Shen family is now a den of wolves
沈二的腿若是保不住
They will be angry with you
沈二的腿是我送你的礼
The prince was ordered to hunt down the Jiang family
沈二是他的军师
沈二出了事
The Jiang family also had a chance
The prince was in a state of confusion
Nature has no time to design you
This is all your chess move.
It seems that Lord Xie doesn't know me well enough.
I can play more than just chess
Will punish evildoers
Appointment at Puhua Temple the next day
Let's understand it better.
沈万
Who are you?
How can we do this step by step?
master
Feng Er lost both legs
How can I live after this?
Daddy and mommy found it
I found the medicine that can cure my second brother's legs.
Too late
Why is it so?
Parents and daughters are useless
How will my second brother live without his legs?
Your Highness
Are legs more important than life?
Disability, improper appearance, prohibition
Stop entering the room as an official
Sister, please shut up.
Second Brother
He is the only genius in my Shen family who has the potential to win the top prize.
Today
It's like being the top scorer in the exam.
And I may not be able to pass the exam
Get out of the Shen family!
The Shen family doesn't have someone as unfilial and unrighteous as you.
Uncle Lian'er is absolutely right.
Don't trust the instigation of people with ulterior motives
Your Highness, your uncle and mother's order
Tomorrow I will recruit Lian's sister into the palace
resist
Big Sin
snort
fine
no
绝对不能让沈莲入宫
Secondary School
You send her away too.
yes
This is the Queen's order.
No one can stop me from entering the palace
snort
Don't even look at what you are.
Entering the palace with this face
All of us in the Shen family will die.
Mo Junli is Xie Yujin's biggest threat
只有沈莲入东宫
I can pull Mo Junli off the horse
Father calms down
There is a magical medicine in the holy mountain that can cover the eight tribes
This has no cure
Can only cover
No cure
If the father wants to cure
I pity my sister and daughter and try to find a solution
Ha ha
Good good good
She is worthy of being my daughter, Shen Zhengyi.
Sui Sui can be considered a great contributor to the Shen family.
But the medicine is three-point poison
This secret medicine contains a lot of saffron and musk
May prevent women from getting pregnant
Unable to conceive
If Lian Er becomes the queen
Do you know the consequences of not being able to get pregnant?
Or did you do it on purpose?
Dad, what are you talking about?
The daughter is devoted to the Shen family
If you don't believe your daughter
Not using my daughter's methods means that she has a clear conscience.
I use
You can heal my face anyway.
There will be no more worries in the future
That makes sense
Lian'er's face depends on you.
If Lian'er could really become the Crown Princess
Your father will also choose a good marriage for you.
You don't have to be careful
father
My daughter wants to marry Xie Yujie, the head of Huangcheng Temple
The Xie family's military power was something the prince specifically requested.
If I can marry into the Xie family
This god horse is really good.
You're attracted to Xie Yujin
It's not that my daughter fell into the water yesterday
It was saved by Lord Xie.
He also sent his daughter back to the bedroom
The daughter doesn't want the Shen family's reputation to be damaged
I came up with this idea
Don't worry every year
There is a big brother
No one dares to chew your tongue
This is a later story
I want Lian'er to enter the palace smoothly tomorrow.
Sister
What to do?
You hate me so much
Or do you want to make me the crown princess?
Who do you look down on?
Your provocation won't hurt me at all
No one can hurt me again in this life
沈莲我告诉你
I can save you
It will destroy you
Dare to do it again
I scratched your face
Sister, I was wrong.
I don't dare
You sleep on the couch
I sleep in bed
Healed the face
Becoming a Crown Princess
I want your life.
You will enter the palace tomorrow
一定要约束好沈莲
We can't let him offend the nobles.
master
I regret it
那沈莲粗鄙无礼
I'm afraid it will implicate the Shen family.
Let's get her out.
ah
There is no regret medicine in this world
沈莲入了太子的眼
Just for the Queen
From now on
According to the method of teaching
教导沈莲有两个拿得出手的嫡女
The Shen family can easily make Liu Ming flourish.
Also staring at the interrogation
I think she has a problem
Shen Wan
Why are you different from what was rumored?
Xie Ci
Are you interested in the eldest daughter of the Shen family?
I heard you say his name these days.
My ears are getting calloused.
I just can't see through him.
Not denying is admitting
Thank you, you are crazy.
The Shen family is the prince's minister
The Xie family is a thorn in the prince's side
沈宛更是人尽皆知的准太子妃
Are you going to sacrifice the Xie family to pursue love?
Talk less to get better faster
Don't die before he cures you.
Thanks, I'm not kidding.
There are wolves in front and tigers behind
We are destined to have no love between children
I know he's willing to save you.
Also because the Jiang family was vindicated
I don't think he's a villain.
besides
I think he's worried about me.
Want to save me from the fire
The emperor is just making a fuss
As for Wan'er, the disciple of the genius doctor
Enough to help him get to the top
But I have to like a wandering folk
The wild girl I just found
Niangniang
反正都姓沈
Since His Highness likes
Why not follow him?
What you said makes sense
Since the emperor likes today's sword bone
If there is no big problem
Let's leave him to be Emperor Liang
Are both of them my brother's daughters?
沈夫人携女眷前来拜见皇后娘娘
Lian Er
This is your first meeting with the Queen.
Be sure to pay attention to your manners
Failure in front of the palace is a serious crime
After the ceremony
You must not stand up unless the queen tells you to.
Don't lie
Remember?
I know, mother.
One
So brave
How dare you deceive Xie Shiyi
Aren't you afraid that the Queen will know?
You are an ugly bastard
Your Majesty, Your Majesty,
May your majesty be blessed with good health.
I pay my respects to Her Majesty the Queen.
Wan'er
Come here soon
Long time no see
It's getting more beautiful
No need to thank the queen
Queen
Why don't you tell me?
When will my luggage arrive?
What is this idiot doing?
Is this the second young lady that the Shen family just found?
Do you still want me to ask you to stand up?
Back to Queen Mother
Sister Lian enters the palace for the first time
Ignorance of etiquette
Sister Lian, get up quickly
Hurry up and get up
Mom, you are biased
Didn't you say that the Queen said you can only stand up when you lie down?
How did you get up by yourself?
So brave
Queen, please forgive me.
The Shen family is like this
Educate your daughter to humiliate me
Queen, please forgive me.
It's all my fault that my father has no way of getting his daughter
My father is willing to accept the punishment
沈夫人如果不会教育女儿
那沈夫人这位子就让别人去做吧
本宫会把人送到沈府
Wan'er
Queen's Aunt
I studied the rules for three months.
Just barely has a look
Now Sister Lian has just come up from the village.
Offline
The Queen's mother sent someone to teach her
You will definitely make rapid progress
have a look
Wan'er can still speak
You
You should learn from your sister.
Let's learn
Thank you Queen for your surrender
More Discipline
Thank you, Queen
Come
This Jinfeng Cloth Kiln
This is the lucky gift I gave you.
See if you like it.
Empress Xie
This pheasant
Even if you put on the Phoenix Feather
I can't become a phoenix
I think only Wan'er is most suitable for this golden hairpin
Wait a minute, the emperor is coming.
You go out for a walk with him.
Cultivate some feelings
Obey the command of this golden hairpin
I'll let the prince put it in for me in a moment.
Wait a moment
This thing is mine.
aunt
You are also biased
I am your niece too.
Besides, the prince obviously likes me.
How can you give it to him?
Dad, this is rude.
An uneducated wild girl
Pull it down for me and get 100
stop
See who dares
The show is about to begin
Take this opportunity to arrange your marriage.
Take the opportunity to reduce Mo Junli's favorability in the emperor's heart
My dear, what are you doing?
This is in the palace.
Ling'er, why don't you come here quickly?
What place do you think this is?
Maternal aunt
You guys are too biased.
Lian Er enters the palace for the first time
How can you not take care of her?
Prince Cousin
You misunderstood your aunt and mother.
It was clearly Sister Lian'er who misbehaved in front of the palace
Shut up, I don't want to hear you talk now.
沈婉你满嘴谎言
Sister Lian is gentle and respectful
I will never bow in front of the temple.
You must have used some trick.
Making Sister Lian look bad in public
The eunuch who was monitoring the six palaces of the emperor has arrived.
Mo Junli, I'm here to lend you a hand
Prince Cousin
Why are you talking to me like this?
You and I are obviously engaged.
snort
I will never marry a shameless woman like you.
The Crown Princess
It can only be a gentle woman like Lian'er
Queen
His Royal Highness the Crown Prince has made up his mind
Please ask the Queen to take back the wedding month
Leave Wan'er with some dignity
If Wan'er regrets the marriage
No one in the entire Shang Kingdom dares to marry you.
You've got to think about it.
The queen mother married a woman like her and brought her home
That's a disaster.
I beg the Queen to take back her order.
good
Then I promise you
Thank you, Governor
Why are you here?
I heard that you entered the palace with Shen Lian
They didn't make things difficult for you, did they?
Thank you, Lord, for caring about me.
I'm worried that you won't be able to keep your appointment tomorrow.
Xiangling died in front of me
oh
It turns out that he cares about Jiang Lin
I'm just being sentimental
Forget it. I won't tease you anymore.
I will keep the appointment tomorrow
Not only will it cure Jiang Lin
I also need to cure your blushing problem when you see people.
The people sent by the master to Anling Village have returned
It is said that the Gu family has already left
I heard he's been gone for many years.
沈婉在撒谎
He's not on his way back.
Knowing your own life experience
But earlier
The owner is assured
We have sent someone to look for him.
We will definitely find the whereabouts of the Gu family
Eliminate the root of the problem
daughter
The prince just said that he wants to keep us here to enjoy the martial arts meal.
Why are you refusing?
Eat, eat, eat
Just know how to eat
Did you know that you almost killed the priest?
Mom, you heard it all.
The prince only recognizes me as his princess
他跟沈万已经退婚了
I will only bring glory to the Shen family.
How could I give birth to such a fool like you?
I really regret helping you get involved.
Fr.
You still have the nerve to argue here?
The Queen had sent someone to scold me a long time ago.
Say I'm bad at managing my household
It doesn't matter who the father and the princess are.
As long as she's from the Shen family
The good daughter of the broken lady
It's all my fault that I'm obsessed
Mother, drive this unlucky star out of the shrine.
I let you suffer
Mother think twice
My sister's birthmark is from my mother
Brought from the womb
We are sorry for her.
What do you mean
Did your mother have any poisoning when she was pregnant?
My sister's birthmark is caused by the accumulation of toxins
It is actually curable.
Since it can be cured
I'll take you down.
teach
I have something to tell Sui Sui
It's Master
Go now!
Just know how to cry
Why lie?
Did you know long ago that she was not the Shen family's biological daughter?
Want to take revenge on the Shen family
It seems that Shen Zhengyi has sent people to Anlin Village
Dad, I'm sorry.
My daughter lied to you.
3 years ago, my daughter met Lian's sister
Only then did I realize that I was not Shen's biological child.
To find the truth
The daughter went to Anlin Village to find the Gu family
What did you say?
40 What frightened you?
Refusing to say anything
Just say that the children were indeed swapped.
Why don't you tell me
I just want to be a priest's daughter
I don't want the world to know about this scandal.
In recent years
I enjoy the glory and wealth
A guilty conscience
Now even my sister is back and the truth is revealed
Father and daughter at their mercy
Why should I believe you?
During this period of time
So many things happened to the Shen family
我甚至怀疑这一切都是你的手笔
To compensate Shen's daughter,
Breaking off the engagement with the Queen
I'm still looking for a pharmacy that can cure my sister's birthmark.
If my daughter tells a lie
Struck by lightning
Can you really cure the birthmark on Lian'er's face?
Well, my daughter has found a good solution
No wish
My sister's face will definitely get better.
As long as Lian'er is cured
I don't care whether you have ulterior motives or not.
I can kill you without any worries
Years old
As long as you work for the Shen family
The Shen family will not treat you unfairly.
I have sent Steward Wang to help you.
Can you cure the birthmark on Lian'er's face first?
good
Missy
These are the herbs that the master asked me to buy for you.
You estimate
You were the one who showed up back then
帮沈成峰打发了重伤的二哥
You caused his leg injury to be incurable.
This disgusting dog leg
Miss, do you have any other instructions?
Manager Wang bought these medicinal herbs
I've spent all my money.
That's a gold ingot.
This little bitch is picking a fight with me
Do you really think I'm a vegetarian?
Miss, you have lived in the Holy Mountain for a long time.
I don't know how expensive firewood, rice, oil and salt are.
Live centipedes, leeches and scorpions that you requested
Too many years
They are all very precious
Centipede Leech Scorpion
What? Who are you trying to poison?
Your Highness doesn't know
This is the recipe that the eldest lady gave to the second lady to regulate her body.
The medicine is extremely precious.
good
You butcher
I think you just want to poison Lian'er
Prince Cousin
Very expensive
I was ordered by my father to treat my sister's injuries.
If you don't believe me, ask Steward Wang.
Yes, yes, not only that
The master also ordered the two young ladies to eat and live together
Just to take good care of the second young lady
I think this set of rhetoric is specially designed to target me.
Go and call my uncle and Lian'er over to me.
Waist
Waist straightened
Chin, chin up.
Reach out
Mother, stretch out your hand
My mother told me not to learn the rules
Please stop bringing shame to the Shen family.
Mom, I'm already the Crown Princess.
Why do I need to learn these rules?
I won't kill you.
I will beat you to death
Beat you to death
daughter
Meet His Highness Uncle
I don't want to be the Crown Princess
Breaking up with the Shen family
Why do you say that, Your Highness?
I respect and love Lian'er
To his relatives, that is also love for the whole family.
But you allowed Shen Wan, the vicious woman, to poison him.
There are indeed poisons in the drug famine
But not all for my sister.
snort
joke
You just said this yourself.
This is the beauty and skin care recipe that Ms. Chen uses for herself.
Water can absorb black toxins
What about this centipede?
It is used to reduce swelling and relieve pain
Plus Scorpion
You can make the unique detoxifying ointment of Muxian Mountain
Your Highness, you can't have
Prejudice He is the disciple of the miracle doctor
It won't kill anyone.
Oh no! The second daughter of the family pushed the lady into the lake.
Caught by the old lady
The second young lady was captured
Let me go
Get lost
Lian Er, are you okay?
Ah, Your Highness
He is not a good match.
Who is Shen Wan?
I know you are unwilling
I didn't choose the people you carefully trained.
But I only have Lian'er in my eyes
I won't make the mistake of looking at people
You can guarantee that you will never regret it in the future
The prince is really blind.
This palace will not marry anyone other than the one who loves you.
I also asked my grandmother not to blame Lian'er anymore.
good
In this case, please ask His Royal Highness
Remember what I said in Shen's house today
Don't regret
I will never regret
但是沈王必须得离开沈家
I will never allow a person with a vicious heart to
Stay with Lian'er
Zong Mo's father has a lot of things going on at home recently.
The daughter is willing to go to Puhua Temple to pray for the Shen family
I hope my father will help me
Dad doesn't have to worry about what's going on at home
Just go to Puhua Temple to find me
You are here
Take a good look at him.
It was fine
I suddenly got a fever.
Xie Yujie
Can you marry me?
What did you say
I just asked the Queen to cancel the engagement.
Right now, all the eligible men in the country despise me.
If you marry me, you will be laughed at by the whole country.
Will you marry me?
It's okay, just pretend I didn't say anything
I'm going to see Jiang Lin
I do
real
I don't know why you said this.
but
I do
Xie Yujin
Marry me
Maybe he'll die.
You are not afraid
I am afraid of death, can you come and heal me?
ah
You two
Talking about love in front of a seriously ill person in a temple monk's room
Aren't you afraid that I will become a ghost and haunt you?
You can't die
When you die and go to hell, you will be chased and beaten by Lord Jiang.
Do you know Lord Jiang?
I followed my master to southern Xinjiang
Hijacked by gangsters
It's Lord Jiang.
Seriously injured, but still came to rescue
Without him
I won't be here anymore.
You don't doubt why I help you
After being rescued, my master and I became military doctors.
Dead bodies everywhere
Rivers of blood
Jiang's army never backed down.
How can I believe they will betray the country?
I'm afraid it's
What are you afraid of?
What are you doing in there?
Shimen, what are you doing in there?
The servant is copying the scriptures
Your Highness, what's the matter?
Lock the door while copying scriptures
What a big rack.
Knock the door open for me.
It's just like what Sister Lian said.
The fox girl who can capture men
Your Highness came to Puhua Temple to inspect the ministers.
I wish you would die here
That's right
I just saw Xie Yujin coming in this direction.
Did you see him?
Wow
Saw it
I saw Mr. Xie.
Where
Young Master Xie led his men over there.
Does that person look like this?
This person has committed a serious crime
If there is any concealment
Treated as equal
Prince brother
Don't scare me like this
I'm a very timid person.
God I'm afraid
Speak nicely to me
I want you to hate me.
Didn't see his appearance clearly
Like a monk
Lord Xie Xiao took him to the vegetarian room.
Go Chase
If he wants to escape
It is also possible to shave your hair and pretend to be a monk.
Go is to walk
Your Highness
沈二小姐醒了
She cried and said she wanted to see His Highness.
Why is Sister Lian here?
It's because you're a vicious woman.
Why did the prince insult me ​​for no reason?
Kamimaru
I found Sister Lian on the plank road outside the city
It's all because you, a vicious woman, bewitched my uncle.
He said he was not feeling well
My uncle sent someone to take him to Muxian Mountain for treatment.
I almost didn't see him.
It seems that Shen Zhengyi is worried
我想直接送沈莲去找师父
没想到沈莲这个蠢货私下通知了莫君
Also, I have already asked someone to ask the minister
Sister Lian is in good health
This is all because of your conspiracy, you evil woman.
Even if you are beautiful
But hidden a vicious heart
I won't kill you.
Because the Shen family is the mother's maternal family
If there is one more time
Don't blame me for being rude.
Pass the order
Don't let the food delivery person come to this Zen room
I want him to fend for himself.
Yes
Ahhh
Why did I marry such an idiot in my previous life?
What?
If he came to Puhua Temple
He must find me to heal his face
Good
Save me from going back to the God's Mansion
Your Highness, how dare you lie to me?
Sister Lian is not sick at all
She is now the main princess of this palace
You shouldn't have lied to her.
Shenwan is about to send her out of Shangjing
Your Highness, please listen to my explanation.
I don't want to hear
The Queen Mother Wants to See Sister Lian
During this time, Sister Rilian will learn the rules in the palace.
Your Highness
I want to see my sister first
Okay, let's go.
snort
The world can never do this
The innocent prince was so disrespectful
I just found out that there are calluses on my face.
Make him finished
Sister Lian has something to tell you
Just make your words clear over there.
真是看我对沈岩做什么
I also picked a place where I could monitor
Don't be afraid, Ling'er
He doesn't dare to do anything to you.
I really didn't let you say this earlier.
This prince is really redundant
Now I bring Ling'er into the palace
The lives of my whole family are in your hands.
You have to help
What shady business are we discussing?
Don't even think about hurting Sister Lian under my nose.
Don't worry, brother
I will definitely look up to Sister Lian
My sister wants to take me into the palace
That's to congratulate sister Lian on having her wish come true.
Sister, I don't mean to show off.
An An, don't cry first
Crying makeup
What if I scare the Crown Prince away again?
I heard from my brother
You have a drug.
Can hide all scars
Sister, please give me the medicine.
If I enter the palace and am found guilty of deceiving the emperor
The Shen family will be executed.
OK
Without father's permission
I dare not say anymore
That demon is going to be extinct.
Don't you know
I know
But isn't it okay to use it in the short term?
Sister, I beg you
I really like His Royal Highness.
I can't live without him
Sister Lin
His Royal Highness
It seems that Jiang Yu has already walked out
This is someone cutting off the source of the trouble.
Thank you for your courage.
What do you mean?
His Highness Wang Chengsi received a secret report
There are many famous actors hidden in Puhua Temple
We went out to capture the actor
I didn't expect to just catch
Just caught someone
Deputy General Jiang came with a group of imperial guards to ask for orders.
His Highness is leading his troops into the army today to turn into a dead
Such a big fuss
Could it be that he is here to grab a seat?
I really want to cheer for Xie Yujin
Mo Junli couldn't possibly say that he came for Jiang Lin.
I can only swallow this anger
Xie Yujin
Are you suspecting that my father is a
Equal
Your Highness,
I am terrified
Fuck your mother's theater
Xie Yujin
I will cut you into pieces
I will report this to His Majesty.
Investigate carefully
If I have wronged Father Jiang
Will be the father's apology
cut
Let me go
Your Highness
I have something to say to Miss Shen.
Acknowledgements
This woman is vicious
You might have been bewitched by him.
A gentleman's friendship
No bad words
Thank you for your reminder, Your Highness
Xie Yujin actually mocked Mo Junli
Not a gentleman
Good job!
Your Highness
Lin Meimei
Ling Er is not feeling well
Marching
Thank you for following the rules every year
It is unreasonable
Mr. Shen, please forgive me.
I have submitted a memorial
It is not possible to ask for Miss Shen
Anyone can speak with their mouth
Who knows if Lord Xie is sincere?
Big brother, thank you for being such a great figure
no sooner said than done
You don't have to worry
This Brother Shen seems to care about you a lot
It's a bit strange indeed
I will pay attention
What are you looking for me for?
Holding the Ten Thousand Souls
This is the Xie family heirloom.
Don't be afraid
This is my token of love for you.
I'm not afraid, it's just that this palace is too precious and too heavy
Can I change my last name to Wang?
This is my keepsake
You are like me
Just change to something light and comfortable
This is the Xie family's business token.
Can command all Xie's businesses
Young Master Xie wants to give me the entire Xie family as a betrothal gift
It turns out that Sister Xie, no matter in this life or in the past
You are so sincere to me
That's the case
Then I accepted it.
Just consider it as my ticket to board your pirate ship
From now on
We are all in this together
Wealth and woe are shared
Be careful of the rampant bandits in Huaizhou Prefecture
Good time for murder and arson
Take care
Huaizhou Prefecture
If the things in Jia Jingui's hand are found out during the interrogation
How bad it is for you and the Shen family!
Today, the Emperor is on the throne
Huaizhou Prefecture Pirates Issue
I will immediately send a letter to report
Let Xie Yujin's knowledge play for you
Go to Huaizhou Prefecture to make arrangements in advance
I will make sure Xie Yujin never returns.
Then I will let you take over the imperial city.
Xie Yuji must die
Marry someone else
前世沈程潇也去了怀中府
I think it was after Mo Jun left him.
I have to find a way to break this deadlock.
Why is my sister acting like a thief?
My cousin the prince loves me too much
Many people were sent to protect me.
It was only late at night that I could find you.
Stop talking nonsense.
Hurry up and apply the medicine film on me
Ice Skin and Jade Bones
Bright eyes and white teeth
Sister Lian, are you satisfied with your face now?
It can actually completely cover
Fate of destiny
Half-Miracle
The things that make you beautiful will also kill you
Sister Lian, let me be frank with you.
This film is not only stunning
And toxicity
Do not stick it on your face for a long time
And you have to change it every 7 days
This prescription is in the hands of my father's confidant, Wang Guanshi.
But my sister
You have to be careful about that network administrator
Why
never mind
I still won't say it.
Tell me now
If you don't say
I'll find my cousin the prince and force you to say no
After all, Wang Guanshi is my father's ancestor.
In the Shen family, he can be said to be a master
Then you still haven't told me why I should be careful of him?
Is he going to harm me?
Lustful
Sister Lian, why don't you go back and have a rest?
Maybe I'm overthinking
After all, he had eight concubines.
Maybe I don't care anymore
Besides, you are going to be the Crown Princess.
He is not a lecher.
God's way.
Makes sense
I'm going back first
Wang Guanshi
If you hadn't embezzled the money my brother spent on leg treatment
He won't regret it forever.
You should die
I thought the prince would return to the palace today.
Only then would they offer sacrifices to allow Xie Yujin to go to Huaizhou Prefecture
I didn't expect him to be so impatient.
Report overnight
Xie Yujin went to Huaizhou Prefecture early this morning
We both didn't say goodbye.
Huaizhou
Emergency
I need to know the Shen family's former residence in Huaizhou Prefecture
Only then can we save Sister Xin Ling
Lian Er
这沈家偏心沈往
Why do you have to go back to the Shen family?
Your Highness' parents are here
I don't want to travel far, I want to go back to my father and mother
Grandma and Brothers Say Goodbye
Enter the palace again or this farewell
See you in a few months.
2Miss
Ling'er, don't come over here
What are you doing, you dog slave?
Your Highness, please forgive me.
The old man didn't do anything
This is a reception.
Miss
Are you okay?
Slave, go away and don't blink
Walk
Chick
If it weren't for your bad face
I won't give way even if I see you
If it weren't for your identity
I'll make you look good.
狗奴才沈小姐叫你还不进去
Hey
Here it comes, hahahaha
The elder sister said that the prescription of the medicine demon is in your hand
Give it to me now
Ask the old slave for help
Must cause death
Make you anxious
Miss
The young lady's prescription was lost by this old servant.
I have to ask the young lady for another one.
The waste is so small
Nothing can be done
Hurry up and get another one from me
Otherwise I will let the prince kill you
Yes, yes, yes
no
Can't get the medicine
You can't enter the palace
Otherwise, this birthmark can't be hidden.
Lin Meimei
The carriage is waiting outside.
It's getting dark.
Don't delay entering the palace
ah
What happened?
Prince Cousin
I suddenly felt like
Maybe he was frightened by that dog slave just now.
otherwise
Let's take a rest in the mansion.
Okay, I will call the imperial physician now.
Wait until you feel better.
Let's leave again.
It was delivered to my door
Then I have to go in next time.
What is Wang Guanshi doing?
Get up and answer the call
Why
Miss, I lost the prescription you gave me.
The second lady was furious about this.
I wish you were in the mansion
Sister Lian is too anxious
Don't take it to heart
I'll write you the prescription.
No matter what, you still have to pay more attention to Sister Lian
after all
He will marry into the East Palace and become the Crown Princess in the future.
There is a bright future ahead
Maybe his father will rely on him to make contributions to the country.
That's right
Does Wang Guanshi have a daughter?
Yes
My daughter
If you are a matchmaker
Married into the East Palace
Being favored by the prince
I can also become the father-in-law of the emperor
Ha ha
Reply to Miss
The slave does have a daughter
Named Whale
But she is now serving as a minister beside the lady.
What a pity that the second young lady just returned home
There's no caring person around me.
If Jingyu could be with her
She will definitely marry into the Eastern Palace as a dowry in the future.
Thank you for your advice, Miss.
If it succeeds
The servant will definitely repay the lady
You don't have to devote yourself to the Shen family.
You are the one who cuts down the defense
If you go back today, you will die.
Hey, who are you?
Why are you with Sister Lian?
Never seen you
Back to His Royal Highness
My name is Jing Yu
The daughter of the king's chamberlain
It was in the wife's body
While serving his father
I am afraid that others will not serve the lady wholeheartedly.
He sent his servants to serve him.
Good looking
It won't scare Sister Lian.
Serve with all your heart
I'll go to Li Changfu to collect the reward later.
Thank you, Your Highness
How dare you seduce the prince's dog in front of me?
Send my daughter to Wucheng
This is for the purpose of being a dowry maid
Flying to the branches
No, I'm going to find Yongqing and sell him out.
This dog
Prince brother's mother came to me today
Said he had something to tell me
I'll go find him
ah
Second Miss
It's you again, you little dog
Someone come here, it's indecent
Ling Er
What happened? Who bullied you?
He once treated me badly
Bumped into me intentionally
It's that dog slave again.
Beat to death
Hey, Your Highness
Your Highness is not
Senior sister, you are finally willing to play with me
It's boring to have the master controlling me every day
Just know how to play
No matter who you manage
This guy is still alive
snort
Can't die
I took the pills you gave me.
Keep him breathing
Well, look
Don't kill me Don't kill me
Your Highness keeps wrongly accusing Steward Wang
rest assured
There's nothing here.
His Royal Highness
Missy
Hahaha Miss
You saved the old slave.
I am grateful to you.
Must repay
Oh yeah
This is what he holds in his hand.
Look
This is the unique code created by Shen Zhengyi
fine
After my rebirth, I figured out most of his secret codes.
this
This is the Shen family's layout plan in Huaizhou Prefecture
Missy
Please deliver this letter to the owner personally.
What's this
Is it important?
If it cannot be delivered to the owner
Young Master
The young master's life is in danger.
Why
The Maharaja's house
you
You didn't really think I'd drag you out of a mass grave.
It's to save your life.
15 years ago, you helped Shen Zhengyi
One of the real murderers who murdered Gu's daughter.
You got it
You cheated the owner
Not only that
You also raped the daughter of the Gu family.
She is my aunt
Got it
What happened to lying to you?
Don't be afraid of retribution for doing bad things
rest assured
I won't let you die so soon.
I have to keep you alive
Seeing the pain of living in Gu's house
I will return it to you one by one
沈长风的腿也是
It's you who harmed the Second Young Master
Shouldn't he?
6年前沈成峰撞伤顾家老二的腿
Because you hid your money
He will never be cured.
He studied poetry and books for so many years and it's all wasted in your hands
He is my second brother
You avenge the Gu family.
Correct answer
As a Reward
I won't let you die
As long as you take this pill
You can't speak
I want you to see it with your own eyes
You all have been punished.
Sister Lian is really smart
I just want a little reminder
She helped me so much.
you say
If Shen Zhengyi was killed by his own daughter
Will he regret his decision?
Senior Sister
Where to go next
Go to Huaizhong to find your brother-in-law
Ye Ning, are you okay?
Why were you able to leave Shangjing?
Brother, I sent someone to disguise himself
I'm catching my fourth sister
No one will notice this time.
And I brought you a gift.
This is my view of Xiaoshidian Stone Peak in Muxian Mountain
I asked him to bring Steward Wang here.
It was Wang Guanshi who caused my second brother's broken leg to be unable to be treated.
Big brother, it's all up to you.
I will not be successful for many years to come.
I will make Wang Guanshi's life worse than death
I want the person you are looking at to be on top
Xie Jia was very sharp that time
Even I can only observe around the post station
Can't get close
What are you going to do?
The Xie family is not easy to mess with
Ah, Master's brother-in-law is so difficult to deal with
Brother, he and I have cooperated for a long time.
And already engaged
Teacher Style
You take your brother to get the network administrator back.
I'm going to find someone
Hey, big sister
Don't be scared
Master's brother-in-law
I
Oh, so scary
His Royal Highness the Crown Prince did this
Nature has his own way
Mr. Shen is both the commander
You listen to him
Wang Chengsi is not planning to rebel, is he?
Rest early
We'll talk tomorrow
Who sent you?
Tell me and I'll spare your life
This is my second time
My fiancé pointed a dagger at my neck
Why is it you?
Is your neck okay?
This is different with a marriage contract
Exchanged tokens of love
Temperament also changed drastically
Last time I got off the carriage
I haven't seen you care about me so much.
I'll get you a glass of water.
I didn't say I was thirsty.
I won't tease you anymore. I'm leaving.
Let's talk business
This letter says that the battle plan has been temporarily changed.
Ask the other party to arrange the killer's attack direction
To prevent accidental injury
这是沈承骁传回沈府的密信
I intercepted it.
沈承骁这两日为我规划的路线
This is exactly
He also arranged for two watercraft
I knew he wanted to use rice to attack me.
I didn't expect there was a backhand
Xie Yujin
沈承骁这次的两艘船
One is an empty ship
There is a picture of the twenty-eight stars on another search.
That was bought from Nanyang by the Shen family at a high price.
Intended to present it to the Queen Mother as a gift
You want that picture
I want you to help me switch the picture while the chaos is going on.
Just consider it as a thank you gift for saving you.
Need not
Put it in the betrothal gift
An assassin came to Xie Duzhu's post station
Knocked out Xiao Si
We need to check
Thank you for resting so early.
Mr. Shen came at an unfortunate time.
Getting ready to rest
Then I'll bother you, Lord Xie.
To prevent the assassins from getting confused
We must search
Mr. Shen, please
Walk
No suspicious persons were found in Mr. Shen's house.
If Mr. Shen has nothing else to do,
Just go back soon.
Don't disturb my rest
snort
But there is one place that has not been searched yet
Mr. Shen suspected that I was harboring an assassin, haha
Thank you, Lord Governor, for joking.
For your personal safety
The bed must be swept
What if I am not the Lord?
Hahaha
If Lord Xie thinks it's okay
That's fine.
Ahhh
Get out of here!
Xiao Gong also came to Huaizhou Prefecture for a tour
Still don't forget to solicit prostitution
You are not qualified to take care of my affairs
Or should I keep my virginity for your sister?
Komiya also joked
But I want to tell you
My sister will not marry you.
Low
snort
Walk
沈小姐啊
You have ruined my reputation in this life.
He is suspicious by nature
I only took the desperate measure of death.
I'll help you clarify
How would you like to clarify this for me?
It's not convenient for me to show up now.
Then I owe you a favor.
The ground is cool
Go back and sit
Use this first.
Who did Master Xie buy this for?
It wasn't bought for me.
Don't be angry
This was originally intended for my mother.
I'll buy it for him later
You never owe me
You came all the way back to save our ship.
I owe you
You don't owe me
I owe you all the people in the Duke's Mansion.
Xie Yujie
Did you know
I'm not from the Shen family.
Would you like to meet my parents?
Daddy and Mommy
You are finally back
I haven't seen you for two years.
Yan Ning
This is his truth.
He actually revealed such a secret in front of me
I'll stay two more days this time.
Accompany you well
good
Your second brother
Why
I'll go see him
Your mother and I will make you something delicious.
That's your second brother.
二哥的腿是沈承峰害的
所以沈承峰的腿伤是你策划的
My second brother was once famous in the literary world
Many followers
Everyone thought he could win the imperial examination.
Shen Chengfeng and I made him like this
No matter how much pain I suffer, I can't empathize with him
Xie Yujian, do you know
Is it the feeling of being pulled from the sky into the house?
沈成峰现在应该知道了吧
This is his retribution.
How long will it take?
Gu Jinghong
Since you are to the world
No regrets
Why not die
Because you can't bear
Then why are you hurt again?
And the family will suffer together
You are the royal son.
You can call on scholars to use their pens as heavy as a thousand pounds
What do you know?
I don't understand
Do you know Jiang Jiajun's second brother?
Jiang Jiajun is my benefactor
They are stationed in southern Xinjiang
Generations of merit
But now the king has issued an order
The prince planned to execute all the men in the Jiang family
The people in Jiang's mansion were locked up and killed.
Why
because
Overshadowing the Master
Brother
Such an inhumane and inactive dynasty
Why is there any need to enter the room?
What can I do?
Why not use your pen and ink
Write the truth about this dark man
Mayfly Power
How can I forgive you?
If my second brother is willing
I can send my second brother to Nanyang
Worship the Immortal Room in Jushan
You mean the master painter?
A literary giant who is famous in the literary world
Jushanxianshi
Brother, remember
I'm not doing this to help you change the situation
I just want my second brother to have light in his eyes
Thanks
This is what I should do
I know
You not only want to vindicate the Gu family
I also want to plan for the Xie family
The soldiers were destroyed
The Xie family sent an army to garrison in southern Xinjiang
As time goes by
They will definitely use the same method to deal with the Xie family
I just want to ensure that armies like the Xie and Jiang families
Able to defend the country
We must also ensure that those soldiers who sacrificed their lives and shed their blood
Not let down
Why
Don't cry.
You still have a battle to fight.
If I die in Huaizhou Prefecture
My mother will take the initiative to come to cancel the engagement
What does it mean?
No one knows your identity
As Di Zhangyong of the Shen family
Even if I don't marry Xie Fu
Not a Crown Princess
You can also marry well you don't have to
Thank you
Before I ask you to marry me
Do you think I should be the Crown Princess?
It's time to fight for the position of Queen
I thought so
The four queens of the Shang Dynasty were all from the Shen family
You can also
Why can't I like you?
Why can't I want to be your concubine?
I am just me
You know my identity offline.
So what do I want to do?
Naturally, no one can control
And everything I do is in my plan.
Including driving me
God King
You know I've always admired you.
Every time you appear, you save me.
You are like a goddess sent from heaven to save me
I'm not some goddess.
I am your wife
Senior Sister, someone is coming towards Gu's house
That's Xie's photo booth.
They came
怕是沈承骁也在找我
I'm leaving first
I have already found someone to erase all traces of the Gu family.
Don't worry
etc.
这是沈家老太爷送给沈承霄的
If there is poison on the viewing ceremony
I think it should be useful
Is there an antidote?
Why are you glaring at me, elder sister and elder brother-in-law?
He is so fierce
You are still young, wait until you grow up.
More vicious than him
Senior Sister Shen's family is not going to kill Senior Sister's husband
He just passed by and it was fine
This is called Mingxiu Plank Road
Secretly crossing Chencang
The Shen family will suffer the consequences
Xianger
Mrs. Xianger
Master, Master
Save Xiaoer!
It's a cross. It's a cross.
Xiao Er is on the boat.
Master, please save Xiao Er
Master Huaizhou Prefecture War Report
The anti-bandit campaign led by General Shen
The whole army was annihilated in the sea area of ​​​​Shengdaoguan
According to my plan
Careful deployment
How did the Shen family caravan fall apart?
The owner of the house received a secret report
The eldest son changed his plans
A few days ago, the letter was sent back to Shangjing by flying eagle.
But was intercepted on the way
We did not receive
So it won’t work.
I immediately went to the palace to ask the emperor to send troops to rescue people.
Go find Steward Wang
He personally trained Shi Shi
I suspect he betrayed me.
snort
Merchant ships planned to be sent to suppress bandits
Bombarded by unknown forces2,100
Merchants and Soldiers
Heavy casualties
This is how you fight bandits.
how
Your sons are on board.
You don't even ask if he's dead or alive.
I'm afraid of you
Is this your sin?
Your Majesty's farewell
Lost the bandit
Regardless of life or death
Everyone has destiny
I just beg Your Majesty to show mercy.
Send people to look for his body
Your Majesty, as a minister, has no time for other things
But there are also gifts for the Queen Mother's birthday on the merchant ship
Those criminals are so bold
I am willing to personally lead the troops to encircle and suppress
Your Majesty
I heard that there are many civilians on the island.
If the indiscriminate suppression of bandits
What are you afraid of?
People
As long as you take refuge in the Water Palace
It's a thief
I have passed 3,000 people
2,000 gun barrels
Please kill the thieves on Holy Island
Kill them all
Your Majesty, Duke of Zheng
I know you are right
But it killed too many of our soldiers.
I want to give an explanation to the people of Shan State
Mr. Shen went back home to clean up.
Let's go. I obey your orders.
Yuji is right
Your Majesty is not a wise ruler
snort
Xie Jiajun, I have to think about it carefully.
The owner of the house, Wan Sangang, was burned
What a coincidence
I heard from nearby villagers that the fire started suddenly.
wrong
Steward Wang should have received the letter that day.
但是被沈莲一句话就给处死了
Call the second lady over.
yes
Householder
The second lady said that he had studied the rules of the day yesterday.
Feeling unwell
Let the family members go find him themselves.
You let him roll over.
Otherwise I'll kill him.
And your family members, please stay calm.
How do I calm down?
Since he came back
Feng'er broke his leg because of his stupidity
Child missing
My Shen family is almost wiped out.
go
Get him to roll over here immediately.
father
Lian Er
What happened on the day when Butler Wang got into trouble?
You tell the truth
That color embryo
He bumped into me.
Trying to be unfair to me
Why go out at midnight?
I get even angrier when I say it.
He inserted his daughter into my room
Attempt to seduce the prince
I blame my relatives.
If the prince's cousin hadn't killed him
How many people in the Shen family were harmed?
If it weren't for the prince's cousin who killed him
Dad and brother broke their legs
Big Brother Life and Death
The department is caused by you.
You have done too much evil
Retribution is upon them
snort
Lock him up for me.
You're not allowed to go anywhere
Master, what are you doing?
he
He said he likes Huang Chengsi's clothes
It's obviously you who asked me to
What is this for?
Does it hurt?
No pain
Seeing you doesn't hurt anymore
Slippery tongue
And he even lied to me together with Shi Feng
I'm not afraid that you won't feel sorry for me.
Was he kidnapped by someone?
Thanks for meeting
I'm afraid
I'm afraid I can't turn things around.
I can't let you get away with it
I'm afraid too
I'm afraid I won't be able to come back alive to see you
Why don't you let your husband put on his clothes first?
Let's talk business
Wear it if you like
Shancheng Xiao has been hidden by Shi Feng
No one can find
Shen Zhengyi spent half his life savings
Bought this painting from a wealthy businessman in Nanyang
The purpose is to present a gift to the Queen Mother on her birthday.
To protect Shen Jiaji's son
Rise to prominence
This is a waste of time.
The Queen Mother really likes this painting.
What do you want to do?
Find Shi Feng and ask him to sell it
Shen Zhengyi spent half his life saving gold
Corruption and bribery are done to the extreme
Although we can't defeat him in one fell swoop
But you can hollow him out little by little
Who do you want to sell it to?
Sold to Yuan Huazhu
Then let Shi Feng tell Yuan Huazhu
On the Queen Mother's Birthday
Take this painting to the county
But isn't the original owner of this painting the opinion of a resident of the mountain?
He is indifferent to fame and fortune
May not cooperate with us
He has accepted my second brother as his apprentice
And I saved his wife.
He won't reject me.
Well prepared, the truth comes out, the Shen family deceived the Queen Mother
The Queen Mother is a daughter of the Liu family
I hate the Shen family.
The Shen family is in great danger now.
Remember I'm leaving here first
Return to Shangjing
You and Shen Chengxiao were saved by the divine doctor of Muxian Mountain
Seriously injured
Poisoned
Go to the street to find
I remember it.
My husband will definitely play this role well.
They poisoned the sea
You must remember to take the antidote first
After this
You are going to resign as the Imperial City Secretary
To save the Xie family
Thank you Miss Ye Ning for arranging a way out for me
You are my person
In my plan
My husband
Then I want him to be healthy.
Subvert the mountains and rivers
Senior Sister
Junior Brother
There is a reason why you are hated in the sect.
The eldest sister, the imperial court, has set off
We will land on the island tomorrow evening
The emperor ordered the massacre
Fortunately, I recruited the pirates in advance.
Arrange for them to retreat
Let them attack the empty island
The Prince of Jin has been trying to find something to hold against the Crown Prince
It is said that the prince is besieging
Use the cannon to shoot the empty island
I guess he will be impeached
Won't
Shen Zhengyi is also here
They will never let Xiao Xi leak out
It is also very likely that the Imperial Guards from Sui will be wiped out.
Shen Zhengyi is vicious
But I also accepted my brother
Let him rescue people
but
It depends on fate.
Prince Jing will definitely like this good show
After returning to Beijing
Prince Jing is the best sword for us to eliminate Mo Junli
Madam Old Madam
The eldest lady is back with the eldest master
Where is your elder brother?
Where's your elder brother?
Brother, he's here.
Ahhh
Mother, little child
My mother and elder brother are seriously injured now.
You dare not touch him
It will hurt like hell
Sui Sui, where is your elder brother injured?
I met Muxianshan's junior fellow apprentice at the entrance to the city.
He said that the master rescued the eldest brother from the sea.
When he was rescued, his whole body was covered with blood.
I was hit by the poison stick on the sea again
I'm afraid my martial arts skills will be wasted in this life.
ah
My little one
Children
He often felt heartbroken by his elder sister in his previous life.
Rejection every day
grandmother
Mother
Don't worry
I will definitely
Try your best to save your brother
Save his life
Bring the people in quickly.
Tiny
Big Brother
Sui Sui, where is your master?
Grandmother and Master went to Yan State
He only asked his junior brother to send the person to me.
But don't worry, grandma
Although I cannot completely clear my brother of his evil deeds
But I will try my best
You guys go back and rest first.
I looked at Xiao Er
Come back when it's late at night.
It's the mother
I want to marry the God King
I can't complete it
Xiao'er, she is your sister.
She is not my sister.
I never considered her my sister.
I can't tell either.
Grandma, don't you know?
But
Suisui has been engaged to Di Changzi from the Duke of Zheng's mansion
This is the marriage that Duke Zheng's Mansion requested the Emperor to grant.
Not afraid of worldliness
I only have the historian left with me
Thanks Yuji
He doesn't deserve it at all
Children
When did you start thinking about him?
From the moment I knew she wasn't my sister
I heard my father say
But she's so pretty.
The national teacher said she was a lucky star
The Shen family prospers because of her
Father's promotion
grandmother
Don't you want to keep her in the Shen family?
It was said before that she was the future crown princess
I buried this thought in my heart
But the ancestor king
Do you want him to go to Xie's house?
Is the Xie family prosperous?
Xiaoer, tell the truth to your grandmother
You have never married
是因为沈婉吗
yes
Grandma, I love him.
If he cannot become the mother of a country
I asked my grandmother to give him to me
I only ask you for this one thing in my life
Can you help me?
Xiao Er
This is not in line with the norm.
You're making things difficult for grandma.
My Body
I can't live without Schwab's medicine
If evil is not accomplished
Then let this matter stay in your heart
Let me stay in bed.
You threaten me
That's all
The Shen family raised him for so many years.
Let him marry you
It's not unfair to him.
I promised
Xie Yuji
My Sui Sui will never marry you
You have someone guarding outside the yard.
I have something to say to the young lady.
Sui Sui sat next to her grandmother
Grandma has something to tell you
Now the Shen family's pattern has changed
沈婉的容貌和各种条件都是上等
Marrying Xiao Er is not impossible
Sui Sui, what do you think of your elder brother?
Big brother is excellent
Why does grandma ask this?
What you enjoy originally belonged to Lian'er.
Because your parents
Caused by mistake
You grew up with your grandmother.
Grandma couldn't bear to send you out to suffer.
What's the meaning
想让我嫁给沈承霄
And the grace of raising me forced me
Grandma has something to say, but it's okay to say it
It's about Big Brother.
Ha ha
Years are smart
Just one click
Your brother's body
It's all up to you
Grandma intends for you to stay with your eldest brother.
Take care of him
grandmother
I am the eldest brother's sister
Don't worry
I will ask the Queen to change your identity for you
This way your arranged marriage won't cause any trouble.
You can still stay in the Shen family legitimately.
Look how good it is
What if you don't want to?
You occupy the position of the Shen family's daughter
Enjoy 15 years
Lian'er is back home
We didn't kick you out.
This is already a great tolerance.
Why are you still unwilling?
Grandma, what do you think?
Are you still thinking about His Royal Highness the Crown Prince?
She also wants to compete with Lian'er for her husband
沈婉你太令我失望了
I don't want to marry the prince.
Then who are you going to marry? Xie Yujin
snort
The doctor sent a message
When Xie Yujin was sent back, his entire body was already purple.
I am only keeping my breath alive thanks to the hundred-year-old medicine
He is the living dead now.
I can save him
I can let him die.
It seems that if I disagree
The old lady won't let me go.
Just you know
You can't go anywhere these days.
I stayed with Xiao'er to take care of him.
You can't resist
You forced me to do this.
You said
You agreed
Right?
That's why you came to heal me
Big Brother
Such a disgusting thing
Even if His Majesty comes to tell me
I won't agree to it.
impossible
Then why do you still come?
Grandmother
Dare not disobey
It's okay
As long as my grandmother is there
You will be mine sooner or later
Big Brother
ah
Sui Sui is not well
Your grandmother fell off the carriage.
The doctor said it was a stroke.
I can't speak now.
Only you can save him.
Send mother over to have a look.
Why is grandma so careless?
How do the people around you serve you?
Sui Sui, please show this to your grandmother.
Your father is back.
Will definitely blame me
There is no cure for my grandmother's illness.
I'm afraid I can only wait on you.
Waiting for a miracle
It's over. It's over.
This master will never let me go when he comes back
Mother, don't be afraid
I will tell my father it was an accident.
Grandma, don't get excited.
I will definitely heal you well
It's worth it that you raised me for so many years
How can your grandmother cure it?
Dad can't be cured
I will hand over the Shen family to you
How do you take care of your mother?
master
It was the mother who accidentally fell off the carriage.
What does it have to do with me?
Father
My grandmother is old.
I was not in good health
Mother has taken good care of us.
It's better not to disturb grandma's rest offline
I need you to come more often.
His Royal Highness
沈婉是你救下了谢玉洁
You are so brave.
It was Master Xie who was saved by my master.
Thank you, young master, you are the pillar of the country
After the loyal minister
I don't know why Your Highness is so angry.
You want to use Muxian Mountain to suppress me?
I dare not
I have been practicing medicine at Muxian Mountain for many years.
Saving the dying and healing the wounded is our duty
If His Highness has any problem someday
I believe the master will not ignore it.
Doctor Li can't be offended by the living dead.
Your Highness, please calm down.
Doctor Li is far away in the mountains
I don't know what's going on in the temple
If it weren't for seeing Dr. Li, it would be useful in the future.
This palace is determined to wipe out the entire Muxianshan clan
snort
never mind
How did you get hurt so badly?
I changed my plan temporarily
The shells were fired directly at my ship.
father
Where is Manager Wang?
I clearly sent back the message.
Steward Wang has committed a crime
Beaten to death
Thrown into a mass grave
Dad, have you sent someone to check it out?
I specially sent Shen Qing to check
It's impossible
I found Steward Wang held hostage on the ship.
You didn't receive the message
He appeared on the bombed ship
Are we being plotted against by a traitor?
impossible
I brought relatives.
Including ambushes and
The network administrator has worked for the Shen family for many years.
It's impossible to be sentenced.
That means there is a traitor in your Divine Palace.
If Lord Shen doesn't get rid of this traitor
Your Shen family is about to face a disaster.
Your Highness, rest assured
I will take care of the affairs of the inner house.
I heard that Xie Yujin was poisoned
Severe coma
Since you are one of my disciples, send her back to the palace.
Do you know her real situation?
It was Junior Sister Chen who sent Young Master Xie back.
He said that the poison stick that Young Master Xie was hit with was more serious than that of his elder brother.
Muxianshan's Antidote
He could only barely save his life.
Your junior brother left medicine for them.
Junior brother brought very little antidote
I sent someone to deliver some to the Xie Mansion.
Next, it depends on the luck of Mr. Xie.
Xie Ci's suspicion that he didn't die that time
The Duke's Mansion is now conducting strict inspections
Is there no way to start?
If Xie Ci could come in slowly
I'm afraid it will delay your highness's plan.
What can I do?
Could it be that I am going to poison him to death?
Shenwan knows medical skills
His Majesty has granted me marriage
It is better to let him get close to the Xie family
They shouldn't be on guard against the young master's bedmate
snort
good
那就抓紧让沈婉嫁过去
As long as Xie Yujin doesn't die
I feel bad.
His Majesty the Emperor has already issued an order granting marriage
I want you to marry early.
father
Sui Sui can't marry into Guan Gong's mansion
Xiao'er, take good care of your injuries.
Dad will definitely avenge you.
Chen Wen, wait for me to return to the palace
Then he will convey his will to the Queen Mother.
Choose an auspicious day for you to marry Xie Yujin
snort
I am a grandmother
Big Brother
Grandma is lying in bed like you.
I don't know why my grandmother is in such a hurry to enter the palace.
Falling off the carriage
The evil wind enters the body
Cannot speak
I have to go see my mother.
She was heartbroken about it.
Big Brother
You better take a rest
I don't believe it. I don't believe it.
ah
I don't believe it
Ah, why is Nanny Song so flustered?
Missy
His Royal Highness Prince Jing brought many people from the Imperial City Bureau
Breaking into the inner courtyard
They also ordered people to surround the Shen family.
Your Highness Prince Jing
Sister Wan, long time no see
Get up quickly
When you were young in the palace
But I don't see you being so distant from me.
His Royal Highness Prince Jing brought his personal soldiers to surround my Shen family
I guess you're not here to reminisce with me.
My sister is so smart
I'll have a good talk with you if I get a chance.
Mother Sui Sui
Go find your father and bring him home.
Xing Er was arrested
He was seriously injured
You'll die.
This king is also looking for Mr. Shen
Take him back to the Imperial City Temple
The Sword King is really a coward
Shen Zhengying was not found
连重伤的沈承潇都不放过
His Royal Highness Prince Niangjing is in charge of Huang Chengsi
If the elder brother is not guilty
He will definitely send him back.
Sui Sui, please beg His Royal Highness Prince Jing
Let him let Xiao'er go.
Wait until Xiao'er recovers
Let Xiao Er go to the Imperial City Division
A place like Imperial City
Anyone who is alive will be skinned alive
presumptuous
When did the Imperial City become your backyard?
You decide when to enter and exit.
How come he is here?
The lady looks good.
Play with my brothers
This ugly guy has no interest in me anymore
What are you doing out here?
It means death and reincarnation
Maybe he can grow up to look like a human
Pooh
That's it
roll
broad daylight
How dare you rob women
Are you okay?
Miss Shen
After Lord Shen returns home
You tell him
The prince and Mr. Shen are waiting for him at the post station
It's His Royal Highness Prince Jing
daughter
elder sister
Who was that man just now?
How come she has a crush on King Jin?
That is the son of His Royal Highness Prince Jin, Concubine Liu
The Queen Mother's family
elder sister
If he were the King of Jin
Does the Queen also have to listen to the Queen Mother?
The Queen Mother is the Emperor's biological mother
Of course you have to listen
So you are familiar with him?
I just heard him call you sister
Just a childhood playmate
He just flattered me.
What is the use of childhood love?
The prince still likes me
Then Prince Jing won't like me either.
What time is it?
You still have the leisure to chat here
Go find your father now.
Right, right, I see. Why are you saying this here?
Aunt Song, go and pick up the horse!
I'm going to find my father
Hey sister
etc.
I'll go with you
Found my father
Didn't Prince Si just say we were going to the Imperial City?
I'll wait for my father.
What time is it?
You can discuss it with your mother.
I'll prepare some money.
Nanny Song, please prepare a comfortable carriage
I want to get into the carriage with my sister.
The carriage is moving so slowly
You want to kill your elder brother?
Mother won't
Prince Jing looks so gentle
How could I hurt my brother?
You don't have ears.
Go quickly
Ma'am, don't listen to him.
Go and get your horse on!
I can't ride a horse.
Shut up, evildoer
No one can stop me from finding a plan
Spare my life.
Don't hit me, please spare my life.
Spare my life
Come on, stop.
You're annoying me
What dirt did you throw at me?
Someone, beat this bitch to death.
Oops!
2Miss, please slow down.
Wash it quickly.
Didn't I ask you to look for the master?
You are
What are you doing
Mother promised to send someone to report outside
Those people followed my father and the Crown Prince.
The family members of the Imperial Guards who went to Huaizhou Prefecture to suppress bandits
There is a lot of buzz outside
It is said that there are no bandits in Huaizhou Prefecture
It was my father who was selfish.
Covet Royal Arms
Kill thousands of imperial guards
Their families came to find them.
ah
Prince, this move is really cruel
Inciting the deceased's family members to come and cause trouble
Complaints
Shake the whole hill
If Shen Zhengyi doesn't die, he will be skinned
What to do?
Don't worry, mother.
I have sent Shen Qing to tell my father
Next, it's up to Prince Jing.
Lian Er
沈宛
You actually allowed these dog slaves to bully Lian'er.
Your prince brother
Ahhh
ah
Ling Er
Your face
Prince
stop
What happened to your face?
Little Miss
Don't let His Royal Highness see his face.
Come on, Auntie Song
Take the second lady downstairs to wash up
Don't offend His Royal Highness the Crown Prince
沈婉
What's that on his face?
I will send him back home
Only stayed for one day
What happened?
Are you trying to rebel against me?
In reply to His Royal Highness the Crown Prince
His Royal Highness Prince Jing brought his personal soldiers
For the sake of the Divine Mansion, I dragged my elder brother away
My second sister and I were originally going to the palace to look for our father.
But I haven't left the gate of the God's Mansion yet
Then someone poured dry water all over him.
The second sister was frightened.
Quickly fetch me some water
I need to take a bath and change clothes quickly
The last king has mysophobia
沈莲这下可是伤了男人心
No, why does it still smell?
Prince Cousin, Don't Be Anxious
All the clothes, shoes and socks in my brother's room have been fumigated with incense.
In a moment
This smell will dissipate.
Your Highness
I heard that my father was summoned to the Imperial City Department by the King of Jin.
I know your elder brother and your father will be fine.
You don't need to worry
Your Highness
I also heard that my father killed many of the royal guards.
Will my father be okay?
You and your father went to fight the bandits
Your Highness must
Will save my father's insolence
Who did you listen to?
Do you know that someone is throwing dirty water on me?
Or was it you who spread the rumor?
Your Highness is wise
今日沈府被人围了
Chen had no choice but to go and get the news
Ms. Chen
The Shen family believes that everyone prospers and everyone suffers together.
Ms. Chen understands
It's all nonsense
The villain King Jin slandered the Shen family
Even if it involves this palace
The Imperial Guards are there to suppress bandits
Death in battle
Your father will be fine.
Mo Junli is so confident
It seems that he has made preparations for both situations.
I have to find a way to inform King Jian.
Prince Cousin
They are all bullying Lian'er
Mother is Lian'er
I will help you out.
Since you've been frightened
Then you stay in the God's Mansion
Take a good rest
Prince's Palace
Don't you want Lian'er anymore?
What you mean is that you don't want Lian'er to go back to the palace with you
Lian'er is happy
Pity enough
Your Highness, you should go and see Sister Lian.
Sister Lian was frightened today
If His Highness is sick again
Your Highness will be distressed again
Don't put the blame on me again.
daughter
My mother called me here so late
I feel unwell.
Year after year
It is God's will that His Royal Highness the Crown Prince can stay in the Divine Palace today
You must seize the opportunity
Wait until you and His Royal Highness the Crown Prince have made a fait accompli.
Mother, I will take care of it for you.
You will be the Crown Princess then.
As for the Duke's Mansion
That Year
Let Ling'er take you there.
Unlucky things
The prince has sent people to evacuate the troublemakers in front of the Shen family
But it didn't take long to disperse
Someone else gathered around.
Still holding Mr. Yu's article
Alluding to what Lord Shen did before
It seems that Prince Jing is very good at seizing opportunities
Yes, people from Wei Zhai.
Request the court to thoroughly investigate the Huaizhou Prefecture's suppression of bandits
The emperor also summoned people to detain him overnight for this matter.
It's all cause and effect.
Be
How is Miss Shen now?
Didn't what happened today hurt him?
只有沈二小姐被迫惨食
Miss Shen dodged
太子的人正在维护沈府的安全
No, I need to go to the temple.
Master, take care of your body
Now the people of the Crown Prince and Prince Jing are keeping an eye on the Divine Palace.
Don't worry, I'll disguise myself.
The situation is grim now
I have to talk to you in person before I give up.
Mainly, I want to see Aning
Missy
Madam asked you to go to the eldest son's room to look after His Royal Highness the Crown Prince.
Your Highness was frightened today.
Jin Yu has 16 chances this year
The young lady's servant is 17 this year
So big
Grandma still keeps you in the house
Could it be that she wants to be my brother's concubine?
My dear, I have never had such an idea.
Please understand, Miss.
I'm not testing you
I just want to give you a chance
Do you really want to stay with this idiot?
Serve him all his life
Please save this slave.
Since my father died
Madam, please give me
Marry the stupid son of Song Mama
I am unwilling but powerless, Miss
Get up, you lost your father
No more support
Marrying him is really helpless
Miss, please save me.
I will serve you like a slave
This incense burner
But it was used to frame me and the prince.
This is your concubine
Coco is the eldest lady
His Royal Highness the Crown Prince doesn't even want you
Why would you need a servant?
He just doesn't want me to be his crown princess
He will not have only one woman in his life, the Crown Princess.
You marry her and become a concubine
With money
Have free time
Why not
But if you want to maintain your position
Climbing into his bed isn't enough
You still need to tell him
yes
Is there something wrong with my eldest lady?
Ah, there is a bug. It's okay.
Okay, Miss, something's up.
Angry they can
Or is it that my wife is worried about her father's safety?
No shape
Now this is being watched by various forces
How dare you come here rashly?
I miss you
Don't be afraid. Things will come to an end soon.
I heard what you said to that maid.
The Shen family actually wants to use dirty tricks
Send you to Mo Junli
You are afraid of this
沈家一直不满意沈莲入宫
I want to bring you and the prince together.
peaceful
How long do you plan to let me lie there?
Lie down until the day you become the Crown Princess
An Ning, I don't want to lie there and do nothing anymore.
Marry me soon
Can I marry you soon?
become
Then I'll go back and prepare now.
You are still injured.
Go back and lie down.
How do I get married?
Now they are eager for me to marry into the Duke's Mansion as soon as possible.
Really
They asked me to marry you early
I'll kill you soon.
As long as I can marry you soon.
Now let's clarify
最大的阻碍是沈程潇那傻子看上我了
Did you know that it was you who caused Mrs. Shen's stroke?
Yesterday, Madam Shen called me over.
跟我说要我给沈程潇做个通防
Old evil woman
What kind of filthy people are the Shen family?
Although I have resigned from the post of Du Chu
但是想让沈承骁死在皇城寺
It's still very simple
I'm going to kill him now.
Don't
Find a chance to give him this powder.
This powder will only make him more painful.
What happens after you eat it?
I guarantee he will be in a coma for ten days or half a month.
Wait for him to wake up
Our marriage is a done deal
I understand that my wife wants him to live a life worse than death.
My wife is so smart
Go back soon
What are you still standing there for?
Wait till I come back to marry you
You bitch
Madam nodded
Give you to my son
I didn't expect you to have an affair
You bitch
I'm gonna kill you.
You get up
You bitch
Look, I won't hit you.
Hit you
presumptuous
You slut, you whore
Ah, Your Highness
Damn, why are you here?
You are not me I was called here from the room
Of course it's here.
Didn't the whale come to you?
I haven't seen a whale.
Whale, this little bitch
Meet His Royal Highness
沈婉你真是令本宫恶心
His Royal Highness
Do you have any misunderstanding about Wan'er?
Misunderstand
沈夫人本宫都知道
本宫对你跟沈府真是太失望了
His Royal Highness
Did you listen to the villain?
Jingyu said
Did you gossip in front of the prince?
The young lady was misunderstood.
You don't, ma'am.
Jingyu
Whale Feather, you little bitch
Dare to recite the book and climb the bed
Wow
stop
He is now my palace's servant.
You move him and try.
Lowly person
是沈宛才对
沈夫人
Do you think
I dare not take action against your Shen family
How dare you be so presumptuous
Your Highness, please forgive me.
His Royal Highness
Forgive this matter
This matter has nothing to do with Wan'er
They are all servants
My father made his own decision
Let Wan'er take the initiative to approach His Royal Highness the Crown Prince
Your father is just trying to preserve the friendship you two had when you were little.
Ha ha
Another uprising
He also deserves
His Royal Highness
Wan'er is the apple of my eye.
You know
What about Sister Lin?
Lian Er
What does this have to do with Lian'er?
沈夫人你口口声声说
沈宛是你们沈家娇生惯养的掌上明珠
What about sister Lian?
You left her out for years.
Have you ever cared about him?
He is cautious
Worry about gains and losses
You as a mother
Only for Shenwan
Where did you put him?
莫君礼倒是将沈莲放在心上了
I have told you thousands of times
I only want Lian'er
But you still insist on doing it
沈婉
You are the one who reaps the benefits
Do you think you have your mother's support?
I dare not touch you
I have no such intention.
Stop pretending to be so hypocritical with me.
You like to hang around
I am not as good as you
His Royal Highness
Please, for the Queen's sake.
Please forgive Wan'er this time.
Spare him
OK
The young master of the Zhenguo Mansion was injured while suppressing bandits
I order you to marry him as soon as possible
Heal him
If he doesn't want
I will make sure you never step out of the Duke of Zhenguo's Mansion.
No
You dare to disobey my order?
Mom, please don't cause trouble for me anymore.
Your Royal Highness
Now you are the only one left in the Divine Palace
You must hold on.
Consider the overall situation
You girl
In the future, she will be brought into the Eastern Palace as a dowry.
Don't have any crooked thoughts
daughter
His Royal Highness
His Royal Highness Prince Jing brought back Master Shi
At the gate of the temple
People talking
沈二小姐冒着危险去了门外
You guys go check it out
What
People come out
Come on, tell us quickly.
Come out quickly
Ladies and gentlemen
Is the Shen family guilty?
The court will punish this king severely
Nor will the soldiers die in vain.
The King will personally monitor
Give you justice
Can you guys go home first?
How could there be such a man who attracts flowers?
It is really the person on the road who is as beautiful as jade as described in the book.
The Prince is Unrivaled
His Royal Highness Prince Jing is right.
What His Royal Highness said just now
This is the determination of my Shen family.
Who are you?
Why do you speak for the Shen family?
I am the second daughter of the Shen family.
She is also the future Crown Princess of His Royal Highness the Crown Prince.
I am going out today to represent the Shen family.
idiot
Where are you in the Shen family?
In this case
You have to give us an explanation.
Did the Shen family kill all the Yuping troops who were suppressing the bandits?
Is it? Is it? Is it?
Speak up, everyone
沈二小姐已经出面
I will definitely give you an explanation
Don't worry, everyone.
Thank you, Your Highness Prince Jing
Your Highness and I have seen your petition.
Your Highness will never allow anyone to kill soldiers indiscriminately.
And my father is still cooperating with the investigation at the Imperial City Bureau
Don't worry, everyone
If my father is guilty
The Shen family will definitely kill their relatives for the sake of justice
No tolerance
If my father really
If you are guilty, our Shen family will definitely kill you for the sake of justice.
No tolerance
好沈爱小姐大意
Of course, if this case has nothing to do with my Shen family
The Shen family will not sit idly by.
My father was the commander-in-chief of the anti-bandit movement.
Many soldiers died
He is half guilty.
沈廉不枉我将你带回沈家
Even if I don't take action
You will still pardon the Shen family
No, this good show must be shown to mother
Mother Mother
Sui Sui Kuai
Call this idiot back to me now
I'm going to kill him
So I opened a warehouse in Shenjiayuan
Take out ten thousand taels of gold
Compensation for the families of fallen soldiers
Pensions for subsequent soldiers
My Shen family will also be responsible to the end
Shut up. Shut up.
Shut him up, sister.
One tael of gold and 10 taels of silver
Do you know how much money is worth?
沈二小姐
How much silver do you intend to compensate each person?
One tael of gold per person
Mother Mother
Hello, mother
OK
Everyone
My mother is not in good health
But don't worry, everyone
I'll take charge and collect the money at the entrance of Shen's house.
Ling'er, you did the right thing.
But you are still young
You go back to the house with your mother first.
这里会有沈夫人此言
诧异本王觉得沈二小姐做的就很好
She is indeed a noble lady from Beijing.
Today, the Shen family's matter has been resolved
It's time for you guys from the Imperial City Division to withdraw.
Lian'er is my fiancée
Please stay away from him.
Your Highness, I am acting on your orders.
After searching here, I will leave.
However, the Huaizhou Prefecture bandit suppression case
I'd like to trouble His Highness to go there in person.
I know.
Ling Er
Today
I really know you now
You are obviously the victim
Yet he is so kind and forgiving of these unruly people.
Unlike some people
Mo Junli, if you ascend the throne
You will definitely not die.
Yun'er, you are the model of a girl from Beijing.
I will report this matter to my father.
Asking for a reward
今日你还是随沈夫人回府吧
It's dangerous outside.
Your Highness is right.
Ling'er, you first
Go back home with your mother
Can't go
Bible Girls Pay Attention to Etiquette
We can't let His Royal Highness Prince Jing down.
His Royal Highness
His Royal Highness Prince Jing
I will take my leave first.
Go fast
Go get the money.
Go Go Go
daughter
Why did you hit me?
Why hit you?
Don't you know what you just said?
How can we afford to compensate others?
Do you think our shrine is a place to cut silver stakes?
daughter
You are so unreasonable.
His Royal Highness Prince Jing
If you didn't send my brother back for my sake
My eldest brother died in the Imperial City a long time ago.
Your face
What face do you have?
Stinks like a demon
Stupid as a pig
Your father's annual salary is only 500 taels
One tael of gold is equal to 10 taels of silver
You lied to me, Shenhu spent money like water
Excessive eating and dressing
No worries about money
More than 2,000 soldiers died
That's tens of thousands of taels of silver.
Even if the priest's house is sold
I can't get that much money.
If you get it together
Tomorrow someone will report that my father took bribes
My father is still on duty at Huangcheng Temple offline
A wrong step
People can't come back.
What if someone found out that my father was paralyzed?
What will happen to us?
Someone discovered that your father was corrupt.
you
You bastard
According to the laws of our dynasty, the number of crimes shall be determined
This is a 10,000-two-
If it exceeds
That means beheading and exterminating all nine generations of the clan.
I don't want to die
The priest's servant told me
The Shen family is particularly good at making money
Rich as a nation
沈二小姐在说什么呢
What is Miss Shen Er talking about?
I didn't say anything.
His Royal Highness Prince Jing
My sister is not feeling well
Can you please let your sister take your mother back to her room to rest?
沈二小姐可要快一些
The people outside the palace are still waiting for your compensation.
Your Highness, rest assured
My father has already arranged it.
Miss Shen, are you satisfied with this play?
Your Highness is joking.
It's the Shen family who's letting His Highness watch the show.
Although I don't know that you and the Shen family
what happened
But the King can see
Your heart is not in this Shen family anymore
Your Highness is really smart
沈宛即将成为谢家心腹
My mind is naturally on my husband's family.
White sister
This prince really doesn't want to see you marry into the Xie family.
Why don't I take a screenshot?
Your Highness is joking again
Your Highness will have 3,000 concubines in the future.
怎会差沈婉之一个
Lend me your good words
I'll tell you good news.
Duke Zheng has reported to his father
Choose a day for you to marry Xie Si
Thank you, Your Highness Prince Jing
Madam, the eunuch beside the emperor
Waiting for the imperial edict.
The master must have been pardoned.
I knew the priest would not lose.
Yes, ma'am, slow down.
Fengtian Chengyun
The emperor issued an edict saying that the son of Duke Zheng thanked
与沈尚书之女沈宛佳偶天成
Specially granted the grace of a parent
The third day of March is designated as an auspicious wedding day
March 3rd
That's the day after tomorrow.
沈夫人接旨吧
snort
It's time to receive the order.
Thank you, my father, for your kindness.
沈夫人是不满陛下的旨意
Are you still not happy about Master Xie Xiao being the son-in-law of your Shen family?
Eunuch Gao is joking.
Fuji Chen is so happy
Just as the minister invites the father-in-law to the wedding
snort
Madam, don't worry.
Zheng Guo Kung Fu is not in decline
If the eldest daughter marries him, he will be considered a member of the Gao family.
Don't worry
高家沈万若是嫁娶郑国公府
What should I do, Father?
I will never do what they want.
The God King is now the lifeline of the God Palace
lady
The Duke of Zheng's Mansion sent someone to propose marriage with the betrothal gift policy.
The people outside the lady's door demanded compensation
The noise started again
Someone sent money.
We took
As for the price
That's not what we said.
只要将沈廉价去谢家便是一石二鸟
I have money
The prince's sister can't go wrong
Open the warehouse and win the offer from the Duke of Zhenguo Mansion
yes
You and I, mother and daughter,
You must take Li Lai
This is the weasel that harmed you.
Mother comes
What's the matter?
I just received an imperial decree for you to get married the day after tomorrow.
The Duke of Zheng sent someone to propose marriage.
The day after tomorrow is so fast
You listen to your mother.
From today
When I came to Xie's house to get married
You can't step out of the boudoir
His Royal Highness is now obsessed
What if he hates Lian'er?
And found Lian Er's birthmark
Then my Divine Palace will surely encounter a disaster.
So, the position of Crown Princess belongs to you.
But the imperial decree granting the marriage has been removed
我们沈府必须要出一个女儿嫁过去
母亲这是要沈莲替嫁
If you can do this
Isn't the Shen family also guilty of deceiving the emperor?
Let your sister marry the prince
That's deceiving the king.
As long as Ling'er marries him
I will ask the Queen for help.
Year after year
Mother, this is for your own good.
Xie Ming
It's to wash the living dead Xie Ci
Mother is not afraid that the Crown Prince will vent his anger on the Shen family
I was thinking
Wait until you and His Royal Highness the Crown Prince have made it a done deal.
Tell His Royal Highness the Crown Prince the truth about Lian Er's birthmark
I didn't expect that Qingyu, that little bitch, would ruin my good thing.
Wait for Ling'er to marry
I will tell His Royal Highness the Crown Prince the truth about Ling'er's birthmark
Men are all lustful.
Then I will admit it
My daughter understands
I will never let my mother down.
Oh, that's right.
After all, our Divine Mansion owes Ling'er so many years.
The betrothal gift of the Duke of Zhenguo
Jewelry Gold and Silver
There are also valuable antiques, calligraphy and paintings
I will remember Ling'er's name.
You owe him what you have to pay with my betrothal gift.
A good fight
good
Then I search for my mother
If it weren't for the fear of alerting the enemy
I really want to tear your face off
The priest is so selfish.
Terrible
Angry
沈夫人想用沈莲给李冲洗
还卖下了你的聘礼补偿沈莲
Let's see what happens
Future Husband and Wife Li Dan
oops
The Xie family has a very solid foundation.
He actually gave so much betrothal gifts.
It just happened to solve my urgent need.
You circled me
Put it under Miss 2's name
Madam, you want to take the second young lady to the East Palace as a dowry.
No
The eldest lady is the future crown princess
Madam wants the second daughter to marry into the Xie Mansion
His Royal Highness will be furious.
The second young lady also wanted to enter the East Palace.
Mom, you have to help me
If it weren't for me
Today you will die at the hands of His Royal Highness the Crown Prince.
You also saw
Since I brought Lian'er into the mansion
The God's Mansion was hit by disasters
Mother-in-law had a stroke
The boss was seriously injured
Broken Leg
Master is in jail
If he were to go to the East Palace
My Father Will Die
The words of the nine tribes of Zhulian
No one can escape
I worship you for years
If the truth comes out
You say it's a bad slave.
The humble master secretly swapped the bride
This way the emperor has a step down
Madam and the Shen family will be fine.
But please take care of my son, Madam.
Mammy
Please get up quickly
Don't worry
Damn, the Shen family has come to this point.
Still calling
fortunately
I have already swapped the house and land deeds in the betrothal gifts
Give it to Aning
My Aning's things
No one can covet
What are the Director's arrangements?
According to the original plan
If the secret guards find something wrong with the lady tomorrow,
Stop now and check for me.
But I believe me
He does that
Madam has already moved the people in the second young lady's room to the front yard.
Get ready for the wedding
Just wait for Lian'er to come over
I drank this drug.
The lady not only gave 1/3 of the betrothal gift to the second daughter
He also took half of his dowry.
Even the golden hairpin the old lady gave you
You put it all in.
You still feel sorry for the second young lady.
After all, she is my own flesh and blood.
Don't treat his mother badly.
I thought of the lady
You should always be dignified and sit down to drink a cup of tea
Sister, let me tell you
I figured it out
Didn't you say we have no money?
I saw that the betrothal gift sent by the Xie family was so much gold and silver.
You just push it out from the inside
back
Ling Er
God can no longer bear your torture
You go to Hohoshe's house
From now on
No one is allowed to approach the second lady's room
yes
idiot
I really think I can control everyone.
沈莲我娘子在何处
Why can't I find him in his bedroom?
You Yaksha
Hand him over to me now.
I found your wife, husband.
Found it
I found my fairy-like wife.
Aqin
I can find you from Huaizhou.
I won't lose you in Beijing.
Your wife can only be me
Wife
It's time to call me husband.
Menglang, please go back soon
Don't let your parents worry
One
Mom, what's wrong with you?
Why are you here?
Whale Cloud
After I was captured
Feed this medicine to the second lady
Why are you here?
Wasn't he called to arrange a marriage?
2Miss, you overslept
It's not daybreak yet
The young lady went out.
Why are you in such a hurry?
I didn't even see her marriage.
How to laugh at her in the future?
Don't worry, Miss
Your fiancé is a servant of the Duke of Zhenguo Mansion, His Royal Highness the Crown Prince.
All these ceremonies cannot pass the royal
Your wedding day will be prepared according to royal standards.
Then I'll ask the Virgin Mary.
How much is his dowry?
I must be countless times more than him.
idiot
How can you compare to Miss?
ah
Mom, what's wrong with you?
Why are you here?
ah
Miss
Madam gave you half of her dowry.
Please don't blame him.
I want to thank my mother, of course.
Missy
Thank you, Mr.
Aren't you the living dead?
My mother said this is a successful flushing
It's fine once the lady enters the door.
Waiting for the return day
I want to thank you very much
Father-in-law and mother-in-law
Aunt Song must have called her the wrong name.
Offline should not be called "little brother-in-law"
Call uncle
Miss, how are you?
how
His Majesty has ordered me to get married.
Should I still disobey the order?
The lady gave half of her dowry
I gave them all back to the second lady.
Doesn't this mean
The eldest daughter brought two dowries
Married into the Duke's Mansion
It's over. It's over.
What?
Is Mammy standing here to teach us how to have a wedding night?
Oh no
No no
Nanny Song should have returned to the Shen family without stopping
There's a good show tonight at the Shen family
Anne
Are you tired?
I'm not tired. I even slept for a while in the sedan chair.
I mean
If you are tired
You can hide in my arms
I will take care of everything in the future
Re-Live
There has been no moment in these six years when I stopped planning
No more resentment
Husband
I'm tired
Let's take a break
Didn't you say it's foolproof?
Or is it that you said yesterday that you would take the blame?
To fool me
lady
No jokes, old slave.
From sending the second young lady into the house to helping her get married
All operated by me alone
I was waiting outside the second young lady's house yesterday.
Unless something
Unless the eldest lady sneaks into the second lady's house
Changed the wedding dress to deceive everyone
Otherwise, I can't figure it out.
The imperial decree for marriage has been issued
Our Shen family must have a daughter to marry.
Mother wants Shen Lian to marry her instead
If you can do this
Isn't the Shen family also guilty of deceiving the emperor?
Let your sister marry the prince
That's deceiving the king.
As long as Ling'er marries him
I will ask the Queen to help me with the
Mother, this is for your own good.
Why he did it
Isn't it good to be a princess?
I'm doing this for his own good.
lady
You gave all those dowries according to the specifications of the second lady.
I also told the eldest lady about the store early on.
The eldest daughter calculated all the dowry.
沈婉这个狼心
Dog lung stuff
I still love her so much.
How dare she plot against me with evil intentions?
Calculating Lian'er's Dowry
I didn't plan to do that.
How long should Ling'er stay in Xie's house?
Xie Ci is a living dead
Wait till he dies
Let's bring Wan'er back.
I'll teach you a lesson later.
Madam, today, the eldest lady came in
Thank you for the successful flushing
Stand up and enter the bridal chamber by yourself
What did you say
Mother Mother
Meng's father died
Mom, I dreamed that my father passed away.
Then you died for him.
Died in front of the coffin
I thought my parents were dead.
So I came to see if you were still alive.
This second lady is really stupid
How can you talk like that?
you
What sin have I committed?
Madam Madam
Prince Jing and the people from the Imperial City Department said outside the door
Send someone out to pick up the owner
Mother
A nightmare come true
They brought my father's body here.
Otherwise, why didn't my father come in by himself?
They are asking us to collect the bodies, mother.
Ah, mother fainted again
What should I do?
Song mother cat, take good care of your mother
I'm going to collect my father's body.
Mr. Shen
Although your confidant has taken all the blame
But the death penalty can be avoided
Living a crime
Lord Shen, as the bandit-suppression commander
Can't escape punishment
This caning
Lord Shen, please don't blame me for worrying too much.
Poor supervision by officials
Personal Affairs
Should
Although Lord Shen can temporarily leave the Imperial City Division
But if there is anything else
I'd like to trouble Mr. Shen to make another trip in person.
That is my duty.
Okay, I'll ask someone from your mansion to pick you up.
His Royal Highness Prince Jing
I am here to collect my father's body.
I don't know where my father is.
沈二小姐何出此言
Your father is fine.
Your Highness, I know
Your Highness is distressed about your subject
I don't want to tell you the truth.
Good intentions
I have nothing to repay you for. I only ask
Lian'er, what do you want?
Your Highness, my father has faked his death.
Find someone to burn him to death.
Otherwise he'll turn into a zombie.
沈二小姐误会了
Your father is not dead.
Not dead, really
My father is still alive
Isn't he a fake corpse?
Mr. Shen can go home for now.
It's just that Lord Shen was injured.
I'm going back to my house to have a good rest.
Your Highness, thank you for sending my father home today.
I have no appetite these days.
Thinking about my father every day
Wake up from the dream today
Dreamed that my father died tragically in the imperial city
What on earth does this idiot want to do?
Silly girl dreams of her mother dying for love
我甚至都没有时间给他们准备棺材
I prepared two copies of the fruit, Your Highness
Ling Er is really scared
沈二小姐的孝心感动天地
I believe he will take good care of Mr. Shen.
The King will leave first.
Your Highness,
Father, please don't commit crimes again.
Ling'er is scared to death
ah
Father
Who is guilty?
Wang Dequan is the only one
Shen Jiajia gave birth to a child
Probably his wife.
Wang Dequan admitted all the guilt.
Sentenced to be executed
In addition to the 40 lashes and the legal annual salary,
No other punishment
Really cheap set
At least 2,000 imperial guards were killed
Husband, calm down
The few people that my elder brother saved have been sent to King Jin.
Do you think
Will the King of Jin let the Crown Prince, the Crown Prince's party, and the Shen family go?
Master, there is one more thing
Yesterday, the second young lady of the Shen family came with an order
Holding a straw mat
Said he wanted to collect Lord Shen's body
Prince Jing, who was escorting Lord Shen back home, saw
Lord Shen is furious
Beat up the second lady in the street
Vomiting blood and fainting
沈怜这蠢货
How could I be deceived by her in my previous life?
Previous life
The past life did not benefit Ajin.
Knowing the hatred in the past life may affect Jin's mood
Let's talk about it later.
You heard wrong
What I said
It was some time ago
Shen Zhengyi is an old fox
Something
This dead end set by King Jin
He can protect himself
I guess he has already discussed the retreat plan with the prince.
Don't worry about the gathering and separation of witnesses and evidence
Prince Jing will also join forces with us
Tomorrow is the Queen Mother's birthday
Will surely defeat them in one fell swoop
It's time for Xiao Geng to offer tea to Bo Tong.
ah
My father is a warrior.
He still doesn't know how badly I've been hurt.
I guess it won't sound good when I talk.
It doesn't matter that Duke Zheng is an upright person.
I won't make things difficult for my new daughter-in-law.
Ah, I wish.
Dad Aning is my biological father
You can't bully him like this.
Why is Duke Zheng so angry?
The confidant Shen Wan pays homage to his father-in-law
Greetings to my father-in-law
If the daughter-in-law does something wrong
Father-in-law, it's okay to say
Don't get upset.
I don't have to scold you
I blame this bastard.
Dad, I'm married.
What else are you dissatisfied with?
Do you really have to make me say it?
That's all
I'm also willing to give it my all
Don't want this old face anymore
yesterday
The imperial physician repeatedly warned you not to have sex.
It's said that it will hurt the body
Even sudden death
And what about you? Have you ever thought about Xie's family?
Have you ever thought about Laozi?
father
Don't listen to that doctor.
I'm not poisoned
Well, your brother-in-law is almost dead.
How come you weren't poisoned?
father
Aning told me that the cunning rabbit died
Running Dog
Xie family honor and disgrace for a hundred years
But he may not become the next soldier
I can only restrain my edge
To save the Xie family
Huaizhou Prefecture Suppresses Bandits
The princelings want to kill me
It was Aning who saved me
We also planned this marriage.
Don't worry, Dad.
I will definitely protect the Xie family
Let your two elders enjoy their old age
Why
I'm old.
You guys did a great job
Ah, mother
I just changed like Ah Jin.
This is a gift from your mother-in-law. Please accept it.
This gift is too expensive.
The bride dared not accept
Oh, it's okay
Your mother-in-law has too many
There are thousands more
Thank you, Gong Dad
Duke of Zheng
Madam Zhou is the only daughter of the richest man in Jiangnan
It seems that the saying that Jiangnan's wealthy businessmen are as rich as a country is not false.
But what about others?
My mother had a quarrel with my father and went back to her parents' home
This marriage was too hasty to come back
You fart
I saw something happened to the Jiang family.
I'm afraid something will happen to your mother.
Just send her to a safe place.
father
Don't worry, Aning and I are well prepared this time.
These traitors will be annihilated
You don't have to worry anymore
good
You guys go down
Doctor, how is my husband's health?
The young master is weak
Try to sleep in separate rooms
If you force the same room
I'm afraid it's not good.
Old East and West End
Did you send grandma to annoy me?
Miss, please drink your soup.
Didn't Nanny Song go back to the Divine Palace last night?
Why are you here again?
Last night, the second young lady in the mansion made a big fuss.
Madam sent someone to look for me.
He told me to take good care of you and my uncle.
I'm afraid you won't feel comfortable in this strange place.
Aunt Song, please be careful with your words
My wife is now a member of my Zhenguo Mansion.
Miss, I have already found out.
The Duke of Zheng's Mansion has prepared a return gift for you.
You just put your dowry in it
Just send it back to Shen's house
Good, Mammy, this is exactly what I want.
But tomorrow is the Queen Mother's birthday
It won't be too late for me to come back after my birthday.
The Shen family will definitely cook some for you at the Queen Mother's birthday banquet.
It can be regarded as repaying the Shen family for raising me.
It won't be too late for me to come back after my birthday.
Mammy
You are late in returning to Xie's house.
Ask him to return the dowry from the stall to me.
Madam, this is what he got.
How can I spit it out?
Mammy, when I woke up this morning
Have someone send your son to Xiao'er's room
Xiao Er is seriously ill
Need someone to accompany you
Waiting for you to return dressed up
I'll send someone else
He sent his wife home
I'll do it for you, don't hurt my baby
No, if it doesn't work out.
Yaozu's life is in danger.
Miss, please save this old slave.
The extra dowry you brought
Those are the second lady's things.
You just need to send your things back to Shen's house.
Otherwise the old lady will hurt our whole family.
Mama, what are you talking about?
This dowry is naturally for the bride.
What's going on with my second sister?
Miss, if you can't bear it
I am unjust.
If you don't do what I say
I will teach you how to cheat your sister of her dowry
Deceiving stepmother
The news spread
As a Xifu
I'm afraid I can't stay here any longer.
What nonsense are you talking about, old slave?
How dare you bully my daughter-in-law?
You are so courageous.
Someone come and lock him up.
Closed in the mountain house
Oh, it's unfair to Zaozong.
In my national martial arts, you must abide by my rules
Help!
Father-in-law
Aunt, I have something to tell you.
Palace but it's okay to talk
Ajin's mother is not here
I think about it
I have to hand over the power to you.
You picked him up.
It just so happens that tomorrow is the Queen Mother's birthday banquet.
You use it to practice.
In addition, all the treasures in the storehouse are at your disposal
My aunt in my previous life gave me three boxes of South China Sea Night Pearls.
Leaving a handle for the emperor
I will never make the same mistake again in my life
master
Why did His Royal Highness Prince Jing take such a heavy hand?
He wants to be in the top
The prince must be removed
Recently, His Majesty has become more and more fond of Prince Jing.
We have to find a way
Win the favor of His Majesty for the Shen family and the prince
The Queen Mother's Birthday Banquet is an opportunity
master
But wasn't the picture of the Star God blown up?
We can't take it either.
A birthday gift that would be more in line with the Queen Mother's wishes.
It's not the bastard you gave birth to.
He actually opened the warehouse to compensate those troublemakers
All the savings from these years are gone.
Master, isn't that your own flesh and blood?
You can't kill him.
If His Royal Highness the Crown Prince hadn't taken a fancy to him
Willing to pay for a painting for us
We can't even get it.
Birthday Gift
If this is discovered
But it's a heinous crime to execute nine generations of the clan.
The truth is destroyed.
That fossil would never appear in the South Seas.
As long as we can please His Majesty this time
All the crises of the Shen family can be solved
沈莲的脸
沈婉治不了
Just find his master
Xie Family
You will be destroyed in my hands
Prince Jing, don't even think about taking the throne
This is a secret letter from Shi Feng.
The Shen family got another painting of the new king of the twenty-eight constellations
Fake
Tomorrow at the Queen Mother's banquet
The treasure owner took the treasure
Encountering a fake
The Shen family's crime of deceiving the emperor was confirmed.
Empress Dowager Liu didn't like the Shen family.
Give him the opportunity to exaggerate.
He didn't try hard to put on eye drops for the emperor
So what do we send?
Night Pearl Mother likes to give Night Pearl to others.
Saves trouble
But I can only give one
Such a precious thing
We are not as rich as the Shen family to afford it.
Thank you, lady
My wife is so thoughtful for me
As a husband, I have no choice but to give myself to you.
Although the evidence is available tomorrow,
But we still can't take it lightly
Go to sleep
After entering the palace
What should not be said or done
Don't do anything
Remember
Mom, I am the future Crown Princess
When I was in the palace
The Queen Mother is very kind to me.
I know everything
Just rest assured
I warn you
Since you appeared
The Shen family is in constant trouble
Today's birthday party is a good day for the Shen family to turn things around
If you made a mistake
I will definitely take your life
Today I am suffering
Congratulations everyone
No need to be formal
Please take a seat.
Empress Dowager Xie
Thank you, Your Majesty
A pair of Jinzhou Changshi Song Dynasty red agate mushrooms with phoenix pattern
The governor of Jingzhou presented a white jade god of fortune, wealth and longevity
Minister of Revenue Li presented a golden birthday gift
Just as the young master presented the East China Sea Night Pearl
Minister of Rites Shen
A painting of the twenty-eight stars of the current mountain immortal
I wish the Queen Mother a happy birthday
May the Queen Mother be blessed with good fortune as vast as the East Sea
Longevity
This picture
Didn't you say a few days ago that during the process of suppressing bandits
Unfortunately lost?
Your Majesty
I know that the Queen Mother has been looking for this for many years.
He ordered his eldest son to go and look for
Thanks to your Majesty
I have retrieved this message
Hurry up and present it to the Queen Mother.
Hey, why is there another picture of the 20 eight stars?
Oh, why is there another picture of the 28 Constellations?
What's the meaning
There is also a picture of the star god
Isn't there only one picture of the Star God in this world?
Father
I guess the ceremonial officer must have registered it wrong.
This disciple is the only suffering in the world
The Shen family went through so much trouble
Just found it for the Royal Grandmother
I saw it once in the South China Sea many years ago.
I didn't expect to see you again in this life
Mr. Shen is thoughtful.
Thank you Queen Mother. It is an honor for the Shen family to share the Queen Mother's worries.
Your Majesty found it
This treasure giver
He is the author of the Twenty-Eight Star Gods Diagram by the Immortal Living in the Mountains
Nominal
He is a painter
Of course I can draw another one
What's so strange about this?
沈二小姐说错了吧
The paintings of the immortals living in the mountains are all unique
How could there be two?
What His Royal Highness Prince Jing meant
One is fake.
Shut up
Mom, what are you doing?
Don't let me say this
Don't let me do that
Now you have a fake
Lost my people
Now you're scolding me
Your Majesty, this painting of Mingchachen is absolutely authentic
Shim Jeongil
You thought I set you up?
Can make you break it so easily
Your Majesty
The painter, the immortal living in the mountains, asked to see
Mountain Immortal
Your Majesty, the Immortal in the Mountain
Residents also seek to see the immortal living in the mountains
That's tomorrow night.
A giant family in the Southeast Asia
Come up quickly, please
Xuan
Grassroots opinion
Bring your disciples to see
Long live the emperor
Long live the moon
Mountain Immortal
Please get up quickly
This immortal from the mountain came with your second brother.
It seems your second brother has let it go.
Long live the Queen Mother
I heard that the Queen Mother really liked my paintings.
On the occasion of the Queen Mother's birthday
Presenting the Twenty-Eight Star Gods
Congratulations to the Queen Mother on this day every year
Every Year Has This Day
The immortal living in the mountains is indeed an immortal
Even the disciples are talented.
It's just that I was outside
I heard that Caomin's paintings were fakes.
I'd like to ask the mountain immortal to take a look.
If anyone dares to lie to the Queen Mother
I will accuse him of deceiving the emperor.
Your Majesty is wise
The Shen family has all the financial resources to achieve this.
There will definitely be no alcohol
As for this immortal who lives in the mountains
Why bring a fake painting?
The minister didn't know.
snort
Are you saying I'm cheating?
You said you bought the painting
Do you have proof?
No proof
But I cannot allow you to deceive His Majesty.
Your Majesty
My paintings were once presented to a nobleman in Nanyang
He said it was worth a hundred thousand gold
Although the common people have not yet entered the world
But I also know
100,000 gold
It is definitely not something a minister of rites can afford.
Please Father, please understand
If Lord Shen can come up with this 100,000 gold
We must find out where this money came from.
If you can't take it out
Then Lord Shen is deceiving the emperor.
Personal
Shen Family Bullies the King
In vain speculators
Confiscate all property
Shen Zhengyi removes the label of massacre
Your Majesty, please slow down.
Caomin's disciple wants to ask Yuan
Your Majesty
Commoner Gu Jinghong wants to sue the Shen family for being unkind
Not only did he snatch the young girls of the common people
He even rode his horse and broke the legs of the common people
Send people to hunt down Caomin's parents
I hope Your Majesty will make the decision for the common people.
It is true
God, you are so brave.
Prince brother
Please save me
I don't want to die with them.
I don't want to live a hard life anymore
Father, we don't know who is here.
How can we trust what they say?
Lord Shen is doing his best for the Shang Dynasty.
Even if there is no merit, there is still hard work.
Father
Yes, Your Majesty
Lord Shen worked hard for the Shang Kingdom
Don't listen to the slander of villains.
Chilled the heart of a loyal person
Your Majesty, I am willing to testify for the disciple of the Immortal Living in the Mountain
Shen Wan
Stop messing around
What can you prove?
Not backing off yet
Your Majesty,
This is the little girl who was killed by Shen Zhengyi 18 years ago.
Gu Jinghong's
My real name is Gu Yan
You are the eldest daughter of the Shen family
Do you know that if you tell a lie
Today, you are the one who deceives me
I know you just married the son of the Duke of Zhenguo
If you deceive the king
Your husband's family will inevitably die.
Your Majesty,
If I tell even a single lie
Willing to die to atone for sin
18 years ago
Shen Zhengyi brought his pregnant wife to Anlin Village
Staying at a farmer's house
Coincidentally, the farmer was also pregnant.
Shen Zhengyi got an ugly daughter
He used his ugly daughter
The farmer's daughter
After he cruelly abandoned his daughter
Also chasing Gu Jia
To prevent future troubles
Shut up for poetry
Stop talking nonsense
I raised you for 18 years
Do you hate the Shen family so much?
Is it because I don't allow you to be the Crown Princess?
没错父皇沈婉嫉妒他妹妹驾驭我
Deliberate lying
Please don't believe him, Father.
Go to receive the report
Xie Yujie, what are you doing?
ah
you
You are Shen Zhengyi's biological daughter.
The ugly daughter
陛下沈廉就是最好的证明
The Shen family also threatened me to marry Xie Xiaogong
To approach him
The words of the servant who poisoned him are true
I hope your majesty will understand
The emperor's son wants to file a complaint
Shen Zhengyi teamed up with the prince to defraud the royal military power
And killed 2,000 imperial guards
Put the father into an unjust situation
Is there any evidence
The son has been found
The Royal Guards who escaped death are waiting outside the palace
Inside the Imperial City Temple
Shen Zhengyi and his men took his place
Crime of deceiving the emperor
Please ask the emperor to execute Shen Zhengyi
With the police effect
Shen Zhengyi
The king committed treason and instigated the prince to be an accomplice to the evil.
Leading to the people's misery
Convey my will
Shen Jia Nan Ding
Repeated exile
The Crown Prince is confined to the Eastern Palace
No will from me
No going out
peaceful
What’s wrong with you
The Shen family has received retribution
From now on, we just need you and I to spend the rest of our lives together.
Xie Yujin
I have a story you want to hear?
Am I in the story?
You are in the story
There is me too
Okay, let's go back to the house.
You talk to me slowly in my arms
After that, take a rest
Strive to give it to my parents and father-in-law as soon as possible
Add a fat baby
Thank God
沈婉重活一世
Saved loved ones, relatives and many innocent people
沈婉定不会辜负您给的机会
The rest of life
I will do my best
Wish the world always happy
Wish you peace forever